<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<collectibles>
    <collectible id="zeke_turters" status="online" img="opponents/zeke_pandoria/extras/turters.png" thumbnail="opponents/zeke_pandoria/extras/turters.png">
        <title>Turters</title>
        <subtitle>Handling a man's turtle!</subtitle>
        <text>The beloved pet and mascot of Zeke and Pandoria. A turtle-like animal that has a habit of wandering around while Zeke is being flamboyant. Look after him, okay?</text>
        <unlock>Play a full game with Zeke and Pandoria from Xenoblade Chronicles 2.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>1</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="zeke_love_manual" img="opponents/zeke_pandoria/6-z_both_hug.png" thumbnail="opponents/zeke_pandoria/extras/love_guide.png">
        <title>Tantalese Love Letter</title>
        <subtitle>Instructions for finding their special interactions...</subtitle>
        <text>Zeke and Pandoria have a few different ways of 'forfeiting' the game.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Normally, they will reach a climax by doing intercrural/thigh sex.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt; If they and every opponent (but the winner) is out of the game, or if they are playing with someone who also has the 'tandem' tag, they may have penetrative sex. There is a random chance this penetrative sex will be doggy style, or kneeling lotus. You should also set your player sexuality tags so that you have some level of 'attraction' to a male opponent.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you pair them with Sucrose, there is also a chance they could show her a good time provided they all lose around the same point...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;  </text>
        <unlock>Zeke and Pandoria have some neat forfeit variations. Win a game against them to get this hint collectible.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>1</counter>
    </collectible>
    <collectible id="zeke_eyepatch" img="opponents/zeke_pandoria/5-zeke_unleashing_power.png" thumbnail="opponents/zeke_pandoria/extras/collectible_eyepatch.png">
        <title>Zeke's Eyepatch</title>
        <subtitle>Holds phenomenal power and looks cool!</subtitle>
        <text>Zeke is the rare kind of chuunibyou who actually has the strength and power to back up his delusions. It's a lucky thing that he's on the good side.</text>
        <unlock>Defeat Zeke &amp; Pandoria in `Eye of Shining Justice' mode. To enable this mode, play with your name set to "King Me", "Queen Me" or "Logos". Or play with them against Giygas during the April Fool's day event.</unlock>
        <hide-details>true</hide-details>
        <counter>1</counter>
        <wearable>true</wearable>
        <clothing img="opponents/zeke_pandoria/extras/collectible_eyepatch.png" name="eyepatch" generic="mask" position="head" type="extra" />
    </collectible>
</collectibles>
