<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.9 at 3:33:49 PM on March 29, 2024. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.9</version>
    <first>Natasha</first>
    <last>Cerebellum</last>
    <label>Natasha</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>28</timer>
    <intelligence>best</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="bobobo">Bo</nickname>
        <nickname for="constanze">Constantinople</nickname>
        <nickname for="critical_darling">Icebreath</nickname>
        <nickname for="default-chan">~name~</nickname>
        <nickname for="helper-chan">Helper-kun</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="stockings" generic="" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="skirt" generic="skirt" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="hoodie" generic="" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="7-defeat">
            <sprite id="defeat-1" src="7-defeat-1.png" x="0" y="0" alpha="100" />
            <sprite id="defeat-2" delay="0.5" src="7-defeat-2.png" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
            <sprite id="defeat-3" delay="2.5" src="7-defeat-3.png" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="defeat-1" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="0" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="1.75" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="2" alpha="0" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="defeat-2" delay="0.5" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
                <keyframe time="1" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="3" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="4" alpha="0" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="defeat-3" delay="2.5" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="0" alpha="0" />
                <keyframe time="1" alpha="100" />
                <keyframe time="2" alpha="100" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>


    <behaviour>
        <persistent-markers>
            <marker>ArmStory</marker>
            <marker>GameStart</marker>
            <marker>PityMode</marker>
            <marker>Cheating</marker>
            <marker>PlayerNoPityWin</marker>
            <marker>Defeat</marker>
        </persistent-markers>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0" priority="900">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PlayerNoPityWin" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="PlayerNoPityWin=0">What're you doing? You've already got maximum bragging rights against me. I don't have anything to give you, so just stop, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="PlayerNoPityWin=0">You're &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; playing with me? I don't have anything else for you. You've seen it all.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="PlayerNoPityWin=0">You know you can stop playing with me now, right? You beat me at my full power. I don't have any secret collectibles or anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="helper-chan" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nice to see you too, &lt;i&gt;"Helper-chan."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">&lt;i&gt;Oops, I caught another case of evilness.&lt;/i&gt; Guess you're just gonna have to beat me again -- and I'm still not gonna go easy on you!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">I dunno how I un-eviled and I dunno how I re-eviled, but here we are again. Gimme your best shot, see if you can beat me again.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Couldn't get enough of my tits, huh? Too bad, I'm evil again. I'm not gonna make seeing them again easy.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So you beat me and you're choosing to play with me again anyway? I'd be flattered if I weren't so, y'know, &lt;i&gt;hilariously evil&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You know I don't have anything else for you, right? You've seen everything. I don't have collectibles or an epilogue or any of that crap, so don't bother asking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Victory&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" weight="7">Am I stuck in a time loop or are you just awful?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" weight="7">Look, I'm happy to keep beating you, but can't you at least, like, change your clothes up or something?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" weight="7">At this rate, I'm starting to think you &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; losing to me. It's not fun for me if you're enjoying it!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" weight="7">I don't care how many times I beat you, I am &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; going to be your "dommy mommy."</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" weight="7">"Nana korobi ya oki." In other words, "I'm going to keep shoving you down."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="GameStart" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" weight="4">Thought you could get rid of me? &lt;i&gt;Nuh uh.&lt;/i&gt; I'm nothing if not persistent.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" weight="4">Bet'cha can't get me out of your head, huh? Psychological torment will do that to ya.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Question: will there be any clothe destruction? 'Cause if not, I'm out.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Buckle up, ladies, this is gonna be one wild game!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">There wouldn't happen to be any broken nose fetishists here, would there? Aw, who'm I kidding, I'll break someone's nose anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">Just say the word and I'll string you up by your feet! People find that sexy, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't get too excited, I'm here to &lt;i&gt;win&lt;/i&gt;. It'd hold no direct value to me, but it's a small victory I just can't let anyone have.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Hope none of you are gonna try to play therapist on me. I'm not troubled, I'm not lonely, and my home life is great. I just like being evil, &lt;i&gt;okay&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">'Sup? I'm like a sadist, 'cept it's not sexual -- my fetishes lie &lt;i&gt;elsewhere&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Luckily for you, you got me and not my sister. She doesn't talk much, but &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; constantly make witty and sarcastic remarks!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">If you're into feet, be thankful you got me and not my sister. She doesn't really have feet. Unless you're into cold, mechanical feet?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Anyone who says bad things about my teeth'll get theirs knocked out! I take good care of my teeth, I just &lt;i&gt;happen&lt;/i&gt; to have an overbite!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Yeah yeah, I know, I have &lt;i&gt;"resting rat face."&lt;/i&gt; Come up with a new one, why don'tcha?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, is this gonna take long? I've got evil things to be doing, and I run a tight schedule. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Doctors say I'm a sociopath. I prefer the term "evil genius."</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I'm all Hyde and no Jekyll.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="GameStart&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" weight="4">You trying to get a collectible outta me or something? Too bad, I'm not giving you &lt;i&gt;crap&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt-extended.png" weight="4">Can't get enough of me and my &lt;i&gt;incredible&lt;/i&gt; grapple arms, huh? Figures.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" weight="4">You following me, ~player~? Fair warning, unlike most people, &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; not afraid to just straight-up kill a stalker. So, y'know, &lt;i&gt;don't stalk me.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="GameStart&gt;=5" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" weight="4">You again? Is it love, or Stockholm syndrome?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" weight="4">Okay, now &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; starting to get on &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; nerves. How many times do I have to encounter you before you get that you can't "fix" me?</state>
                <state img="#-confused-extended.png" weight="4">You're not trying to get my grapple arm blueprints outta me, are you? 'Cause it's not hard to figure out. &lt;i&gt;Every&lt;/i&gt; evil genius knows how to make them.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" weight="4">What're you, trying to be my apprentice or something? Well it ain't gonna happen. You can't teach evil.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" weight="4">Seriously, ~player~, stop trying to "fix" me. I'm not broken!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" weight="4">It's official. I'm stuck in a time loop with this ~player.ifMale(guy|chick)~...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nice to see you too, &lt;i&gt;"Helper-chan."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="112">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="barnette_leaving" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Jura_Barnette1">That's your girlfriend, huh? I think we both know you can do better than &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_deselected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Oh well. I must've scared ~target.ifMale(him|her)~ off.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I get it. Not everyone can handle playing a game with a super villain.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! Why'd you deselect ~target.ifMale(him? I wanted to torment him!|her? I wanted to torment her!)~</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I don't share my table with quitters anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is it normal for people to wander in and out like that? I would've thought people would know where they're going.</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png">Make up your mind already, ~player~! I'm not waiting around all day for you!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, good riddance. I could smell ~target.ifMale(him|her)~ from &lt;i&gt;here&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">Don't worry, I'll keep the next one from getting away! I'll just tie 'em up!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">That's right! Run while you still can!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Okay, I know I'm not the most conventionally attractive, but c'mon, I'm not &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; unattractive.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Quick! Start the game before ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ comes back!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="91">
                <condition role="opp" character="aqua_grunt" />
                <condition role="opp" character="magma_grunt" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="TwoGrunts_Intro">&lt;i&gt;Henchmen?&lt;/i&gt; Really? And from two different groups? You guys can't even agree on who to be an underling for?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Natasha_Intro" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="CD_Intro">&lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt; Scared of me already, that's what I like to see! I'll spare your jaw -- &lt;i&gt;for now&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="dust" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, an anthro... Never did care for furries...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, an anthro. I hate anthros... I mean I hate a lot of things but I always know &lt;i&gt;why&lt;/i&gt;. Not so with furries...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, a furry... Can't you just have, like, a &lt;i&gt;normal&lt;/i&gt; face?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, an anthro... My uncle was killed by an anthro bandicoot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="Revy_Smoking1">Ugh, smoking? Really? I may be evil, but I don't kill, and second-hand smoke is &lt;i&gt;basically&lt;/i&gt; chemical warfare. That's against the geneva conventions, you know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="ae86" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hah. Nice car. &lt;i&gt;Not.&lt;/i&gt; That thing was outdated in the &lt;i&gt;90s&lt;/i&gt;, so it's basically a fossil now, and not even a good-looking one!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Hey, nice shoe box. &lt;i&gt;Oh wait, that's your car.&lt;/i&gt; If you're gonna drive an old car, you could've at least gotten something &lt;i&gt;nice&lt;/i&gt;, like a 1958 Cadillac Eldorado.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="monique" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Who invited the mime? Oh well, guess I'll just have to do enough talking for the both of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="1" role="other" character="natasha" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! Me! You can't be here! Go back to your own universe!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh, an impersonator, huh? How about we go toe-to-toe and see how well you copy me?</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">Dang, I knew I looked good, but &lt;i&gt;dang, I look good.&lt;/i&gt; Weird how much a mirror takes away from how you look.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, you the chick I'm based on? Nina... something-or-other?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="2-" role="other" character="natasha" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is this the part where I fight copies of myself to overcome... something? I don't exactly got anything to overcome, though. I'm pretty happy with myself.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Is the multiverse collapsing or something? There shouldn't be this many of me in one place.</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">Aw man, just think of how much tether we have between us right now!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">Hey, how's about we see which one of us is from the universe where I'm stronger than all the other versions of me? I bet it's me!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Glad to see my multiverse counterparts are still good lookin'. It's a real win-win for ~player~ over there.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmmm... Guess I'm from the universe where I'm not diggin' the duplicates. I'm supposed to be one of a kind!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Someone here smells like the ocean. I &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; the smell of the ocean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="streaming-chan" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Streaming this game without the consent of any of your opponents? That's evil! &lt;i&gt;I love it!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="gray" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Stripping before we even start? Ha! You &lt;i&gt;fool&lt;/i&gt;! You're gonna lose before I even strip down to a casual look!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami_szs" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nuh uh! You're not getting me with that nonsense! I've met enough evil school girls to know that you're probably hiding a space parasite in your torso or something!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nuh uh! You're not getting me with that nonsense! The "evil school girl" schtick is more common than you think. You're hair is probably super lethal or something!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Wait, seriously? There's &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; special about you? You don't have a spirit fighter or evil hair or anything like that? At least tell me you're secretly a pop star or something!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Wait, seriously? There's &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; special about you? Are you at least from some kind of super prestigious school where you gotta literally be the best in the world to get in?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="rainbow_dash" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh. Rainbow hair. I should've though of that... Oh well. Pink rocks too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="other" character="sakura" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You're really think you can hide the smell of a zombie from me? &lt;i&gt;Do you know how many undead peers I have?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Isn't it ironic that I look more undead than you, where I &lt;i&gt;strive&lt;/i&gt; for the very same look you're hiding? Ditch the makeup, love who you are, you dumb zombie!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="spooky" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Huh. First time I'm seeing a ghost that isn't haunting a robot or something. They're... cuter than I expected.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yuelia" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">A butterfly?... A freakin' &lt;i&gt;butterfly&lt;/i&gt;? I like The Fly as much as the next guy, but being turned into an insect isn't a super power! You should be spending your time trying to be human again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="mary" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ducks? Why're you putting ducks in your -- oh, crap, sorry, I was reading too far ahead. Let's start over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="amalia" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">I don't care how many of you nature chicks I meet, you'll never convince me that chlorokinesis is a cool power!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="turandot" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Turandot_Intro">Ah, the illustrious "Princess of Death." Gotta say, I'm quite the fan.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="90">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="aqua_grunt" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="magma_grunt" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Grunt_Intro">A &lt;i&gt;henchman&lt;/i&gt;? Really? What, is your boss not strong enough to do &lt;i&gt;his own&lt;/i&gt; dirty work?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Question: will there be any clothe destruction? 'Cause if not, I'm out.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Buckle up, ladies, this is gonna be one wild game!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">There wouldn't happen to be any broken nose fetishists here, would there? Aw, who'm I kidding, I'll break someone's nose anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">Just say the word and I'll string you up by your feet! People find that sexy, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't get too excited, I'm here to &lt;i&gt;win&lt;/i&gt;. It'd hold no direct value to me, but it's a small victory I just can't let anyone have.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Hope none of you are gonna try to play therapist on me. I'm not troubled, I'm not lonely, and my home life is great. I just like being evil, &lt;i&gt;okay&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">'Sup? I'm like a sadist, 'cept it's not sexual -- my fetishes lie &lt;i&gt;elsewhere&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Luckily for you, you got me and not my sister. She doesn't talk much, but &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; constantly make witty and sarcastic remarks!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">If you're into feet, be thankful you got me and not my sister. She doesn't really have feet. Unless you're into cold, mechanical feet?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Anyone who says bad things about my teeth'll get theirs knocked out! I take good care of my teeth, I just &lt;i&gt;happen&lt;/i&gt; to have an overbite!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Yeah yeah, I know, I have &lt;i&gt;"resting rat face."&lt;/i&gt; Come up with a new one, why don'tcha?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, is this gonna take long? I've got evil things to be doing, and I run a tight schedule. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Doctors say I'm a sociopath. I prefer the term "evil genius."</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I'm all Hyde and no Jekyll.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Victory&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="PityMode" set-intelligence="average">This line activates pity mode. I don't want to be &lt;i&gt;unbeatable&lt;/i&gt;, 'cause then it'd be even sweeter when I win ten times in a row!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="PityModeEnd" set-intelligence="">
                    <text>This line deactivates pity mode. Enjoy losing again!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Victory" op="=" value="0" />
                        <marker name="Defeat" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="GameStart">Don't mind me, just spying on how many games you play with me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-humored.png">Ha! None for me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Gimme ~cards.text~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="19">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">&lt;i&gt;Would you look at that, another good hand. I'm so surprised.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">I never get tired of coming out on top!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Think you've finally got me beat this round? I can guarantee you don't!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="20">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh. A pair's not exactly solid. Not sure how I ended up with that...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Only a pair, eh? Should'a got better than that, but I guess I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; still at the mercy of chance...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">The heck? A pair? I should be doing better than &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="21">
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Aw crap, I miscalculated something somewhere...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Crap, this hand didn't turn out how I meant it to... Don't try and tell me "It's karma!" Karma isn't real! I would know!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">That's life right there: No matter how smart you are, no matter how many correct moves you make, you can get screwed over with total junk.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="71" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="music" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Revy_Music1">Lemme put on some industrial screamo for ya. It'll make your ears bleed!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="72" totalRounds="4-">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="killing" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Revy_Killing1">&lt;i&gt;Really?&lt;/i&gt; You don't know if &lt;i&gt;I've&lt;/i&gt; killed before? I've done things &lt;i&gt;worse&lt;/i&gt; than murder!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="87" totalRounds="8-15">
                <condition role="other" character="caitlin" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="Thank_The_Dealer" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Caitlin_Claping1">Do you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; want &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; to clap? With &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt; hands? I mean I'm all for making horrible clanging noises, I just want you to know what you're asking for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" stage="5-9" saidMarker="Stripping_RivalTalk" sayingMarker="Followup_RivalArm" notSaidMarker="Misc_InventorInjuries" />
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Not as cool as mine, I bet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" stage="1-9" saidMarker="Invention_HumanPotion" sayingMarker="Followup_Vampires" />
                <state img="#-humored.png">Oh yeah, real smooth recovery, Helper-kun -- &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="50">
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" stage="0" sayingMarker="PortalMaster" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">"Portal Master," huh? Can't say I've ever heard of those, but I'm good at learning my enemies on the fly, so it doesn't matter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="53">
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" stage="2-5" sayingMarker="Prompt_Sleepwear" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I dress like exactly what you'd expect a girl like me to dress like when she sleeps. And that's all I'll say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="scm" stage="0-8" sayingMarker="scm_natasha" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="SCM_ToothDis1">Heh. Alright, I'll admit, that one was &lt;i&gt;almost&lt;/i&gt; clever.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="110">
                <condition role="other" character="nadeshiko" stage="0" sayingMarker="Nadeshiko_WhereareWe" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Nadeshiko_Inventory1">Oh, you didn't know? We were all kidnapped by some psycho, forced to play strip poker for ~player.ifMale(his|her)~ own sick pleasure. None of us know where we are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="111">
                <condition role="other" character="nadeshiko" stage="4-6" sayingMarker="NadeshikoPartnerPreference" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="Nadeshiko_Partner1">How close-minded of you to assume I even &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; a "partner." What next, you gonna ask me how many kids I'm gonna have after I get married?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="51">
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" saidMarker="PortalMaster" sayingMarker="PortalMaster_Explain" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Oh, that's all? Just a mage? Like I'm afraid.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Advice_DiscontinuedToys" sayingMarker="Followup_Recontinuing" />
                <state img="#-humored.png">Ha! Denying people what they want for no reason other than "It wasn't making enough money." Capitalism at its finest!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Misc_UniverseMap" sayingMarker="Followup_Volunteer" />
                <state img="#-arm.png">Funny, nosebleeds are also a normal side-effect of me punching you in the nose!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Villain_NatashaCerebellum" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="CD_VillainNatasha">You blow a fuse or something, Icebreath? &lt;i&gt;I'm right here!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Villain_Jamie" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="CD_VillainJamie">Ha! Yep, I know that chick. She's so coarse to every that no one wants to help her out of that shackle! Doesn't bother &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, of course, but I enjoy her struggles too much to help!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Villain_RavenVonGrimblade" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="CD_VillainRaven">Real shame about him. That sword of his gives him &lt;i&gt;so much&lt;/i&gt; destructive potential. What a waste of an ancient magical artifact!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Villain_Wereshark" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="CD_VillainWereshark">Nah, she doesn't rob banks anymore. She's Von Grimblade's girlfriend now, he's helping her learn to use her powers for good. Like turning into a shark is good for anything other than eating people!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="52">
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" sayingMarker="Prompt_Giant" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Sure, why not? The bigger I am, the bigger my potential for destruction becomes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Natasha_BrokenArm1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Helperchan_BrokenArm1">Yeah, I'm gonna go with "No, accidents don't count." Is that all ya got, Helper-kun?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="18">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Natasha_Hacking1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Helperchan_BrokenArm1">Hmm... Hacking isn't really &lt;i&gt;mean&lt;/i&gt;, more like &lt;i&gt;malicious&lt;/i&gt;. If that's all ya got, I &lt;i&gt;guess&lt;/i&gt; I'll count it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="10" totalRounds="0">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="Intro" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Intro">Oh, we're actually giving out names here? Alright. I'm Natasha. Surprised ya didn't already know that. I'm a pretty big villain.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Intro">You've probably heard my name on the news enough times, but I'm Natasha. And if you haven't seen me on the news before, I'm known for bad things. Lots and lots of bad things.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Intro">You've probably already heard of me, but I'm Natasha Cerebellum -- yes, the daughter of &lt;i&gt;Dr.&lt;/i&gt; Cerebellum, the guy who made robot arms possible.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="Intro">You know how some people just want to watch the world burn? That's me. Hi. Natasha Cerebellum.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Intro">Oh, we're giving out names? Well then, I'm... Natasha. Yeah, let's go with that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="13">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="7-" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">What if I told you I'm going easy on you right now? You have no way of verifying, so you'd just have to take my word for it!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hope you're liking my winning streak! Or I guess, "Not-losing streak?" Whatever.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="11" oneShotId="12">
                <condition status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="NoNonCon">Oh, hey, by the way, I may be evil, but non-con is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; my thing. I save the life-ruining stuff for people I &lt;i&gt;truly&lt;/i&gt; hate.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="12" oneShotId="9" priority="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Arms" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="MoreArms">These aren't my only pair of arms, by the way. I've also got a stripped-down version of these that I can wear sleeves over, and I've been experimenting with a bigger, badder pair too.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="GrapplingIsThePinnacle">Shame that a grapple feature is, like, the pinnacle of mechanical arm gadgets. Sure, you can stash just about anything in them, but nothing is quite as practical as grapple arms.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="LargerArms">I've been trying to figure out how I can give myself bigger mechanical arms. The weight is inclined to pull my arms outta their sockets, but supports would just get in the way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="17" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NoCursing" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="MiddleFinger">Sure, putting up a middle finger can be an easy way to upset someone, but that's &lt;i&gt;incredibly&lt;/i&gt; trite and not nearly personal enough for my tastes.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="AdultWords">Seriously, can you believe some people actually get mad if you don't curse? "Use your adult words," they say. "Expand your vocabulary, you myopic troglodyte," I say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="49" oneShotId="11">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Cheating" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="CheatingIsHard">Frankly, you should be &lt;i&gt;impressed&lt;/i&gt; I've been cheating. You have any idea how hard it is counting cards, making sure I don't pull something that shouldn't be possible?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="75" oneShotId="33">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ToyingWithPeople" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="RedMarket">I'd actually &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; to shutdown the "Red Market" -- y'know, human trafficking, hitmen, that kind of stuff. Not for the sake of doing what's right, but because it'd deny people things they want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" id="18">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="8" marker="NoCursing">If it bothers you that I don't curse despite being a full grown adult in an adults-only situation, then mission &lt;i&gt;freakin'&lt;/i&gt; accomplished! It's just one of many little things I do to get under people's skin!</state>
                <state img="#-confused-extended.png" oneShotId="10" marker="NoFunnyBusiness">In case it wasn't already &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; clear: I'm dangerous, so don't try anything "funny," alright? Or do! Give me a reason to bust your jaw!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="13">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1" marker="NoKindBones">In case you're wondering, &lt;i&gt;no&lt;/i&gt;, I &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; have a single kind bone in my body. Bones aren't kind, &lt;i&gt;stupid. Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="2" marker="BeatinNBruisin">Any chance any of you are into BDSM? Beatin' and bruisin's kinda my thing. Well, more of a hobby than a fetish.</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png" oneShotId="3" marker="EnoughTether">Any of you into being tied up? I've got enough tether for everyone!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="4" marker="ILikeFire">Anyone mind if I get a fire going? I'm not cold, I just like fire.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="5" marker="GrizLegs">I'm gonna kick Grizelda's butt if she's not resting when I get home. Her legs are gonna fall apart without a tune up...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="6" marker="WontDitchArms">Don't worry, I'm not gonna ditch my arms just to pass another round. What kind of &lt;i&gt;weirdo&lt;/i&gt; would do something like that?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="7" marker="NoBuckTeeth">Hey, just so you know, I find the term "buck teeth" offensive. "Overbite," "rabbit teeth," and "super muncher" are fine, but "buck" invokes the imagery of a deer's ugly freakin' antlers and I won't stand for it!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="16" marker="PlayTheClassics">One time I pulled that "bucket over the door" prank just for the heck of it. Sometimes you just gotta play the classics.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="17" marker="ToyingWithPeople">Contrary to popular belief, I actually &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; people. I just love toying with them more!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="18" marker="NeroForteFail">Shame Nero Forte's dead. It was fun watching him &lt;i&gt;fail horrendously&lt;/i&gt; at being a hero! Seriously, that guy caused more destruction accidentally than I do when I'm &lt;i&gt;actively trying&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="23" marker="MorningCoffee">You know what's fun? Talking to people before they've had their morning coffee! Super easy way to annoy people! Joke's on &lt;i&gt;them&lt;/i&gt; for becoming reliant on caffeine!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="119" marker="BadEndings">I love how upset people can get when their favorite piece of media doesn't end how they wanted it to! People can be such slaves to their own expectations sometimes! It's hilarious!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="490" marker="SuddenDeath" font-size="small">Don't forget, at any given moment, you could suddenly drop dead. You could suddenly have an embolism, or spontaneously combust, or some kind of freak accident could come along and take you out in an instant.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png" oneShotId="591" marker="VerySuperExtremelyEvil">In case I haven't said it enough or it wasn't clear: I'm evil. &lt;i&gt;Very&lt;/i&gt; evil. Like &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; super freakin' evil.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="593" marker="CopsCantStopMe">By the way, don't think that calling the cops will help you. &lt;i&gt;Obviously&lt;/i&gt; if super heroes aren't enough to stop me, regular police won't be either! And even if I go to jail, I'll just break out again!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="626" marker="InnocentBystanders" font-size="small">Here's a villainy pro-tip for ya: An easy way to distract your opponent is to endanger innocent bystanders! Gets 'em every time!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="721" marker="RememberToForget">Hey, remember that thing you're trying to forget? An embarrassing moment, maybe? Personal failing? Buy something you feel guilty about, perhaps? Hope I jogged your memory!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="831" marker="SleepForever">Hope you enjoy you're sleep tonight. For all you know, when you go to bed tonight, you'll &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; wake up.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="1011" marker="DormPopcorn">When I was in college, I used to make popcorn in the dorm microwave all the time. The smell made people &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; mad! The fact that popcorn is a tasty snack is just a bonus!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1205" marker="BrokenFormatting">Would it make you mad &lt;br&gt;if &lt;br&gt;I broke formatting rules for no reason? &lt;i&gt;No?&lt;/i&gt; ArE yOu SuRe?? &gt;:)</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1206" marker="ToddlerSlang" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="smaller">Hey, real question, why are adults talking like toddlers now? Using words like "nuggies" and "chocky milk?" Is that supposed to counter-balance all the children who curse or are people just actively &lt;i&gt;trying&lt;/i&gt; to make me wanna break their "fingies?"</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1228" marker="ManualFunctions">You're now manually blinking. And manually breathing. And you're now aware of your tongue.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="1251" marker="CorperateGreed">Friendly reminder: Corporate greed is rampant, destroying the planet and shortening your lifespan little by little all for a quick buck, and there's nothing you can do to stop it.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="1275" marker="TwistedLegacy">Remember, you'll either die a meaningless blip in history, or be remembered long enough for your legacy to be twisted and exaggerated into making you out to be a monster.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="1378" marker="CatchingFlies" font-size="small">"You catch more flies with honey than vinegar." You ever stop to think that it's not because honey is sweeter, but because it's &lt;i&gt;stickier&lt;/i&gt;? And either way, you're &lt;i&gt;catching&lt;/i&gt; them, not &lt;i&gt;coercing&lt;/i&gt; them -- it's bad for them either way.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="1379" marker="WillyWonkaMovies">Look, I know you don't wanna accept it, but the fact is, the Gene Wilder Willy Wonka movie was a horribly inaccurate adaptation that only existed to sell you candy. The Johnny Depp one is superior in every way.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1432" marker="TrustAndLies" font-size="small">You ever think about how even those you trust probably lie to you? Telling you "I'm fine" when they're suffering emotionally. Telling you your art's good when it's not. Telling you they care about you, but not more than the average passerby.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1504" marker="DogMoms">If any of you own pets, I just want you to know how sad and pathetic it is to call yourself its "parent." &lt;i&gt;No, you are not its parent, you did not birth it.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1526" marker="LongWindedJokeThatProbablyWasntEvenWorthTyping">Hope you're having an easy time keep up with what everyone's been saying, ~player~. I mean, some people can sure talk &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt;, it can be tough keeping up with what the topic is and if the train of thought you had before you got interrupted is even still relevant, or if you can even remember what that thing was in the first place. Yeah, I know I'm not the first character to do this gag, and I'm sure I won't be the last, but I'm trying to prove my point while simultaneously trolling you with dialogue that you might not even bother to read in the dialogue log. Also, at least for me, the game doesn't continue until I finish what I had to say, so I'm holding up the game for everyone else too. And if you actually bothered to read all of this in the dialogue log, the joke is still on you for being that much of a bozo for dialogue that you'd make sure you've read &lt;i&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt;, even long-winded trolls like this. &lt;i&gt;Bozo.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1558" marker="DoYourselfAFavor">I hate when people try to recommend something by saying "Do yourself a favor" or "You owe it to yourself." How about &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; do yourself a favor and avoid making me wanna give you a black eye!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="7" oneShotId="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Prompt_MeanestThing">So, what's the meanest thing you've ever done? Personally, I've done so many mean things that I can't pick just one "meanest."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="14" oneShotId="2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="HateConformity">I hate a lot of things, but you know what I really, &lt;i&gt;truly&lt;/i&gt; hate? Conformity. People mindlessly doing what everyone else is doing. Don't you just &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; that? If I catch any of you doing that, I will smash your toes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="16" oneShotId="3">
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="Arms">Yes, the arms're metal, and yes, they're cold. Wanna feel?</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="Arms">Yes, the arms're metal, and yes, they have weapons stashed in 'em. Wanna see?</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="Arms">Get a good look at my mechanical arms yet? These bad girls are packed with a flamethrower, a bomb launcher, and my special "chaos cannon!"</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png" marker="Arms">Get a good look at my mechanical arms yet? I can detach 'em at each joint for grappling, and I can electrify every inch of the tether!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="8" oneShotId="14">
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Prompt_MakeMeAngry">Y'know, despite being so &lt;i&gt;incredibly&lt;/i&gt; evil, I'm actually pretty chill most of the time. Go ahead, try and make me angry! I bet'cha can't!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="15" oneShotId="5">
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Multilingual">I love when people try to talk in secret around me by using another language. The look on their faces when I chime in regardless because I speak that language too never gets old!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="37" oneShotId="19" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="7-" notSaidMarker="Cheating" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="FriskForCards">Tired of my winning streak? Think I'm cheating? You're free to frisk me for cards. You won't feel a thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="70" oneShotId="20">
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="HotdogNotSandwich">By the way, a hotdog is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; a sandwich. Nor are tacos, lunch wraps, or hamburgers. Whatever argument you have against this is incorrect.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="76" oneShotId="24" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" filter="dc_comics" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="NotScaredOfSuperman">Honestly, if Superman were real, I bet I could take him. Kryptonite doesn't exactly seem rare, and all else fails, I can prey on his desire to protect people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="36" totalRounds="28-" priority="0">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Can you hurry up and lose the game already? I've got people to keep miserable.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Listen, there are people out there I need to ensure are miserable &lt;i&gt;at all times&lt;/i&gt;, so can you hurry up and lose?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Can we wrap this game up already? I've got sick and twisted things to do to people who may or may not deserve it.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Look, I'm a busy villain, so can we get this game finished already? The sooner we're done, the sooner I can get back to causing public mayhem.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">This gonna take much longer? I've got billionaires to torture -- not for money, just for my own amusement.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" hidden="1">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="4" notSaidMarker="PityMode" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" set-intelligence="good">This line brings my AI down a bit so I'm easier to beat. Don't want you whinin' about me being unbeatable in bug reports.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" hidden="1">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" notSaidMarker="PityMode" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" set-intelligence="">This line resets my AI, provided I'm not winning. Theoretically, this &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt; make beating me feasible without compromising the believability of my cheating.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="59" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! Stop poking around in my dialogue!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" hidden="1">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="PityMode" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" set-intelligence="">This line resets my AI, ideally preventing me from losing nine times out of ten. Pity mode exists for a reason.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" id="105">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="natasha0" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="Meia_Misidentified1">I think you're playing a game you can't win, &lt;i&gt;Rei -- oh I'm sorry, I meant "Meia."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="60">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="natasha0" />
                <state img="#-confused-extended.png" marker="Revy_Threat1">Is that the best you can come up with? A threat of unlicensed dentistry? You realize I could do the same to you from across the room, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="107">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="natasha0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Jura_Proclamations1">Is that really any different from announcing &lt;i&gt;"I'm the prettiest, most desirable girl here"&lt;/i&gt; when &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; show up?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Natasha_Human1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="CD_Human1">Yes, I'm human -- and before you ask, yes, it's all natural, and so is my hair.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" sayingMarker="Natasha_Inventions1" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Inventions1">Nope! Where's the fun in having someone else do your evil for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="82">
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" sayingMarker="Natasha_Rival1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Helperchan_Rival1">Are you sure you didn't just go to high school with &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;Crap.&lt;/i&gt; The odds of &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; being the first to lose are, suffice to say, &lt;i&gt;not good&lt;/i&gt;. This shouldn't be possible...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confused.png">You actually got me once. Dang. You're already surpassing expectations -- which, granted, is easy to do when expectations are extremely low.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh. I actually lost once. I didn't miscalculate, did I...?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Huh. Didn't expect to lose, but naturally I have a contingency plan: Take my clothes off. &lt;i&gt;Duh.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Inga ouhou, I suppose. No, I don't care if you don't know what I just said.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-3">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="11">Huh. You got me again. That's almost impressive. No, really. You're playing against an evil genius here!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="12">You're not cheating, are you? 'Cause that would be evil, and then I'd have to give you kudos!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="13">How much would you hate me if I pulled out one of my teeth to pass this round? I'm not gonna do it, I just wanna know how mad you'd be!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="14">You're lucky I value my arms. Do you realize how many nuts, bolts, and wires I could be pulling out of them to stall with?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="70">Y'know, I'm not used to losing. It's a nice change of pace!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="662">Did you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; beat me this round or did I just &lt;i&gt;let you&lt;/i&gt; win? I'll never tell.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="758" font-size="small">This would be the part where I'd blurt out an advertisement just to screw with you, but like &lt;i&gt;heck&lt;/i&gt; am I gonna actually waste breath talking about a real product from a company that'd &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; think ads in strip poker are a good idea.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well crap, I really didn't think I'd lose this much...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Really didn't think I'd lose this much. My only contingency plan is "Keep taking off my clothes..." Eh, I'm not worried.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm actually being pushed to the edge of defeat. That's never happened before... What an interesting feeling.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">What, you think I'm afraid to show my tits? &lt;i&gt;Yeah right!&lt;/i&gt; My tits are fantastic!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Seriously? What, did I not cheat hard enough?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Crap. Should've known probability could screw me over in this...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You want a naked super villain? Fine, I'll give you one!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-humored.png">Hey, you're actually getting me out of my underwear now. &lt;i&gt;Yes, stockings are underwear.&lt;/i&gt; I will fight you on that!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">So I'm running out of clothes. Do I look like I care?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="913">La yulda il-momen min gohr marratein... No, I don't care if you know enough Arabic to know what I just said.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0" id="83">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helperchan_Rival1" />
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Natasha_Rival1" sayingMarker="Natasha_Rival2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Helperchan_Rival2">Are you sure? Memory can be a fickle thing. Maybe you just forgot these things?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="CD_Human1" />
                <condition role="other" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="Natasha_Human2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="CD_Human2">Nope! I'm perfectly healthy -- could probably live 'til I'm 100, even! My skin and hair have always been like this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Dreamcatcher_Inventions1" />
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" sayingMarker="Natasha_Inventions2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Inventions2">My arms, for one thing -- well, technically &lt;i&gt;two&lt;/i&gt; things. You won't find prosthetics likes these on store shelves, especially because they contain my special "chaos cannon."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="108">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Cheating" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Victory&gt;=3" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating=0">
                    <text>Hey, ~player~, remember when I said I was cheating? I lied. Luck's just been terrible to you.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="CheatingC" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating=0">
                    <text>Wanna know something funny, ~player~? I haven't actually been cheating, you just suck at poker.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="CheatingC" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating=0">
                    <text>Remember when I said I was cheating, ~player~? I lied. I only said that to mess with your head, but really, you've just been unlucky.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="CheatingC" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="79">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Cheating" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating=0">
                    <text>Ready to see them again, ~player~? Maybe &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; the cheater this time. Can't be &lt;i&gt;luck&lt;/i&gt; that's gotten you here again.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="CheatingB" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating=0">
                    <text>Guess this'll be nothing new for &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, ~player~. I don't believe &lt;i&gt;luck&lt;/i&gt; has gotten you here again. I think you're &lt;i&gt;cheating&lt;/i&gt;.</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="CheatingB" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Victory==1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="SelfishEvil">You may think what &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; do is selfish, but aren't we all? Sure, you may do &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; things, but is it not so &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; feel good, or avoid feeling &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="SelfishEvil">You may think villains like me are selfish, but &lt;i&gt;everyone&lt;/i&gt; is selfish. At the end of the day, we're &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; just doing what feels good to us. Good and bad are just perspectives.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You're gonna have to try &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt; harder than that to see my underwear. As you can guess, I don't like making things easy!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="NoScars">Hey, instead of trying to peek up my skirt, why don'tcha take a good look at my face. Notice how it's free of scars? That's 'cause scars are for people who get in over their heads, which never happens to &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="WhatKindOfEvil">So, be honest, what kind of evil things do you think I get up to? Stealing purses? Robbing banks? Maybe killing, just for the fun of it?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="WhatKindOfEvil">Be honest, when I say I'm evil, what do you think that means? Am I just some thief? A vandal, maybe? Or perhaps a cold-blooded killer?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="OrderOfBozos">Those "Order of Heroes" bozos make me laugh -- I mean, &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; authority figures make me laugh, but those guys in particular. They think killing villains is the key to stopping crime. &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="RootOfAllEvil">Y'know, it makes me laugh when people call money "the root of all evil." Pah! "&lt;i&gt;All&lt;/i&gt; evil," they say.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Now's the part where you see I actually have really frilly, delicate panties on that makes you see my character differently, huh? &lt;i&gt;Yeah right!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">What kind of panties do you think I have on? Skull-patterned? Black and white stripes? Maybe something pink and frilly?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="PastBully">Growing up, I had this "bully." Wouldn't stop making fun of my teeth and skin. You wanna know what I did?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="PastBully">Believe it or not, &lt;i&gt;I have&lt;/i&gt; been bullied before, when I was young. Kept making fun of my skin and teeth. You know what happened to her?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="BrokeOuttaPrison">I've been to prison before, you know. Broke out, of course. Like I was gonna live out &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; sentence.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="RuinYourDay">Isn't it interesting how much easier it is to &lt;i&gt;ruin&lt;/i&gt; someone's day -- or year or &lt;i&gt;life&lt;/i&gt; -- than it is to "make" it?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="YourLifeIsYourOwn">Do you think you're unique, ~player~? No, really, do you think your life is really &lt;i&gt;yours&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="9">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Prompt_ArmStory">So what do you think took my arms? Car crash? Lab accident? Or maybe some crazy bet I lost?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Prompt_ArmStory">Any guesses as to what took my arms? Freak accident? Mishandling a lawnmower? Maybe some rogue neighborhood dog?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Prompt_ArmStory" font-size="small">I bet you think some super hero made me lose my arms, huh? Ripped 'em off with super strength, or perhaps they got overzealous with their magic, or maybe even tricked me into hurting myself with my own invention?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Too bad for you, I've got a bra on! Gotta keep the girls in place when I'm out swinging around kicking people in the face!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Keep it in your pants, I've got a bra on under this. Why &lt;i&gt;wouldn't&lt;/i&gt; I have a bra on under this?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This is my favorite shirt, but I'm willing to sacrifice my material possessions for the greater bad. Also I have a bra on, so I'm still denying you what you want.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="WorldOfHate">I know you're not going to accept it, but the truth is, the world &lt;i&gt;runs&lt;/i&gt; on hatred. Think about it.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="WorldOfHate">You probably like to think the world runs on love and kindness, or maybe some kind of desire to "always do better." &lt;i&gt;Wrong.&lt;/i&gt; It runs on &lt;i&gt;hate.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="WorldOfHate">You might think the world would be better off without hatred, but you couldn't be farther from the truth.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="MonsterArt">Don't you just &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; how often it comes out that someone involved with a piece of media you enjoy is actually a horrible monster?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="36">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating">Confession time: I've been cheating this whole game. I've got cards hidden in my arms. The fact that you got this far is almost impressive, so I won't deny you what you came for.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating" font-size="small">Alright, honesty time: I've been cheating this whole game. There's cards in my arms. But I'm nothing if not a woman of principle, so I'll see this match through to it's end. I came here to win, and that's what I'm gonna do!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating">Allow me to soil this &lt;i&gt;lovely&lt;/i&gt; moment with a confession: I've been cheating at this game. I stashed some cards in my arms. But I'm not about to run away. You'll get your nudity.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating">How about I give you some boobs &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; some truth: I've had cards stashed in my arms this whole time, been using them to cheat. I'll still give you the nudity you so &lt;i&gt;desperately&lt;/i&gt; need, though.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Cheating">To think, I've been cheating this whole time, and you're still gonna see my boobs. That's right, I'm &lt;i&gt;cheating&lt;/i&gt;. Obviously luck has gotten the better of me, but I'm not mad. I'll give you what you're owed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Whatever. I'm &lt;i&gt;far&lt;/i&gt; too persistent to back out now!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Yes, I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; petty enough to want to win here. Winning is something that's nice, and I can't let anyone have anything nice!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Before you ask, no, I &lt;i&gt;won't&lt;/i&gt; give you a view from behind. You should know better than to ask me for anything nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You're lucky I don't stink. As easy as it'd be to torment people by having poor hygiene, I much prefer when people realize that the chick who just thrashed them smells better than they do!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="StrongLegs">I'm really not much of a leg-centric girl. I mean, &lt;i&gt;clearly&lt;/i&gt; I let my arms do most of my work. I can kick ya so hard it'll knock the wind out of ya, though!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="StrongLegs">Make no mistake, disabling my arms won't make me helpless. I can still kick you hard enough to knock ya out.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="StrongLegs" font-size="small">Don't make the mistake of thinking I'd be helpless without my arms. I'm prepared for &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; contingency, including those in which I must rely on my legs.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="HeckThePolice">Tell me, ~player~, are you one of those law-abiding anti-police civilians? "Screw the police!" "The only good cop is a dead cop!" One'a those people?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" priority="0">
                <condition count="5-" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="GameStart&gt;=2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="FourPeopleOverpowering">Do you normally play this game with four opponents, ~player~? You ever think about how easy it is for four people to overpower one person and do terrible things to them?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1" id="84">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helperchan_Rival2" />
                <condition role="other" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Natasha_Rival2" sayingMarker="Natasha_Rival3" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="Helperchan_Rival3">Ugh, you're no fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Dreamcatcher_Inventions2" />
                <condition role="other" character="dreamcatcher" sayingMarker="Natasha_Inventions3" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Inventions3">It starts a sub-atomic domino effect that causes a forceful explosion wherever I aim it, with unpredictable lightning offshoots as a natural byproduct!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="64">
                <condition role="opp" character="helper-chan" saidMarker="Natasha_Cheating1" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="Helperchan_Cheating1">And what are you gonna do about it, Helper-kun? &lt;i&gt;Call Diego over?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" priority="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FourPeopleOverpowering" />
                <condition count="0" filter="non-human" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">"You don't have a reason to do that," you may think. Oh but you forget, &lt;i&gt;we're humans.&lt;/i&gt; We'll find &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; reason to justify it. It's what we do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="23">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ArmStory" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="AlreadyToldArmStory">
                    <text>Why not ask ~player~? ~player.ifMale(He|She)~ looks like a good guesser!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="ArmStory" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="AlreadyToldArmStory">
                    <text>Weren't you paying attention? I already told you! Not &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; fault you can't remember! ~player~, why don't &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; remind them?</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="ArmStory" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="AlreadyToldArmStory">
                    <text>~player~ is the know-it-all here. Why don't you ask ~player.ifMale(&lt;i&gt;him&lt;/i&gt;|&lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt;)~ what happened to my arms?</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="ArmStory" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="AlreadyToldArmStory">
                    <text>&lt;i&gt;Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot to ask the puppet master if I have permission to exposit. May I share that story, ~player.ifMale(master|mistress)~ ~player~?&lt;/i&gt;</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="ArmStory" op="=" value="0" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="ArmStory=0">In actuality, it was just a simple lab accident... &lt;i&gt;Oh, I'm sorry, ~player~, is that not what I told you before?&lt;/i&gt; Guess it's been retconned.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="ArmStory=0">I lied to you before, ~player~. Actually, I lost a wrestling match to a psychotic robot who kept my arms as trophies. I totally thrashed him in the rematch, though!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="ArmStory=0">I lied before, ~player~. The sad truth is, my father used me as a guinea pig for his cybernetics experiments. Jokes on &lt;i&gt;him&lt;/i&gt;, though, I used them to kill him!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="ArmStory=0">I didn't wanna tell ya this before, ~player~, but actually, I lost my arms in the same car crash that killed my parents. Don't worry, though, I found the other driver eventually! Needless to say, he's dead too now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WhatKindOfEvil" />
                <state img="#-threatening.png">&lt;i&gt;Wrong!&lt;/i&gt; I'm the kind of psycho who'll make you &lt;i&gt;wish&lt;/i&gt; you were dead! I'll turn your life into a waking nightmare just for kicks!</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png">&lt;i&gt;Wrong!&lt;/i&gt; I'm the kind of psycho who'd kill everyone you love first, and make sure you live a long, miserable life after!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Nah, that stuff is child's play. I'm more into making everything and every&lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; you hold dear crumble before you while you watch helplessly.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" font-size="small">Nah, killing is for losers with inferiority complexes. Dying doesn't give your enemy enough time to suffer. What ya gotta do is make sure they're completely incapable of feeling an ounce of joy ever again.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Well, let's just say that I'm less like a bullet to the head and more like a slow, terminal disease with no known cure.</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png">Sure, I may stab you, shock you, or burn you. I may even tear you limb from limb. But with &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, you're not &lt;i&gt;allowed&lt;/i&gt; to die!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Maybe, just &lt;i&gt;maybe&lt;/i&gt;, I enjoy denying people what they want so much that I even deny &lt;i&gt;other villains&lt;/i&gt; what they want too, circling back around to being heroic.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I'm the best kind of evil: Not someone who does bad things for monetary gain, political influence, or social status, but just for the fun of it. In a way, I'm like an artist.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PastBully" />
                <state img="#-threatening.png" marker="Bully_BurnedHouses">&lt;i&gt;I burned her house down -- twice.&lt;/i&gt; She didn't think I'd find her new house, &lt;i&gt;but I did.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png" marker="Bully_BrokenSpine">&lt;i&gt;I broke her spine.&lt;/i&gt; Even with modern advancements, she'll never feel anything below her neck &lt;i&gt;ever again&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png" marker="Bully_HadADog">Let's just say, she had a dog -- &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt; a dog.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="WorldOfHate" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png">You &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; to be hungry, so you eat. You &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; to be tired, so you sleep. You &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; injustice, so you fight it. Hate is &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Hate drives us to change things. If you hate something, you strive to erase it, or correct it, or be better than it. Without hate, we become complacent and apathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">A lack of hatred wouldn't mean contentment, it would mean &lt;i&gt;complacency&lt;/i&gt;. You can't tell me it'd be better to be &lt;i&gt;apathetic&lt;/i&gt; to social injustices than it is to &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="OrderOfBozos" />
                <state img="#-arm.png">Part of their logic is that the death sentence serves to scare people out of being a villain. I'm living proof they're wrong!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Haven't they heard "Locks only keep honest people out?" Figuratively, of course. In this case, the death sentence is the lock.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You'd think they'd realize they're just creating a cycle of vengeance and despair. &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; supposed to be the one doing that!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You'd think after they had one ex-hero commit a big massacre in their own base over the issue that they'd start to reconsider.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">It's like they never read "What's So Funny About Truth, Justice and the American Way?"</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Did you know that 3% of people on death row are actually innocent? Imagine how much bigger that number gets when you apply the penalty more freely.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="StrongLegs" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I'd give myself mechanical legs to match my arms, but I'm wary of that whole "Turning myself into nothing but a brain in a robot body" slippery slope.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm pretty mobile with my grapple arms, but I have considered making jet boots to get a better speed advantage.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">You should see the mechanical legs I built for my sister. Her knees are scrap cannons!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">And no, that's not an invitation to say "Step on me, mommy." I'm not gonna step on you if you'll enjoy it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="BrokeOuttaPrison" />
                <state img="#-arm.png">They have these power-suppressing collars, you know. Didn't work on &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, though. My intelligence isn't the result of a power.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">They couldn't diagnose me with anything, so they couldn't medicate me, which only left me mentally clear to jury-rig a new set of grapple arms to break out with!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Prison made the mistake of treating me like a person -- you can thank Golden Glory's push for prison reform for that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NoScars" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm one of those villains that's always thinking several steps ahead of you. The only things that'll happen here are things I &lt;i&gt;allow&lt;/i&gt; to happen.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">I'm one of those villains that's always thinking several steps ahead of you. Don't believe me? Why don'tcha take a swing at me and see what happens?  Go on, make it a good one!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">At any given moment, I have &lt;i&gt;at least&lt;/i&gt; three contingency plans ready, including... Yep, that exact situation you're thinking of right now, ~player~. You don't even have to say it -- you're not as clever as you think you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="CheatingB" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I get it. There're no other breasts quite like these. Small, perky, blue. You just &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt; to see them again.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">You turned on cheat mode so you could see nudity faster. Maybe you're not even paying attention to what I'm saying. I get it.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">How many times is enough for you? Twice? Three times? 'Til they don't turn you on anymore? And then what, you just move on to someone else, rinse and repeat?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Maybe you don't care about them at all? Maybe you're just trying to see all of my dialogue? Or find a secret collectible, maybe? Well tough luck, I don't have any.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You think I don't notice what you do here? And I don't mean the ~player.ifMale(jerking|jilling)~ off, I mean all the &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; stuff. You really think you're doing the right thing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="CheatingC" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Well, you're seeing my breasts again, so at least you have &lt;i&gt;a little&lt;/i&gt; luck... &lt;i&gt;for now.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Well, you got this far again. Maybe &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; the cheater?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Or maybe I'm lying about lying and I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; cheating? You'll never know!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Don't you just hate that luck's been on &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; side this whole time?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">You know what else? My name's not even "Natasha!" You're so freakin' gullible! Like I'd just &lt;i&gt;give you&lt;/i&gt; my real name!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">You really believed that, just like you really believed me when I said my name's "Natasha Cerebellum" -- that my &lt;i&gt;brain surgeon&lt;/i&gt; father would &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; have a name &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; apt. You're so gullible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SelfishEvil" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">If doing good things makes &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; feel good, isn't that a form of selfishness? Would you stop doing good things if doing them started to feel bad?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">If I do bad things for good reasons, are they still bad things? If I &lt;i&gt;enjoy&lt;/i&gt; doing bad things for good reasons, am &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; still bad? Where do you draw the line?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">What about people who do good things for bad reasons? Is their good still valid? What about someone who does good things &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; bad things? Is &lt;i&gt;their&lt;/i&gt;good invalidated?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; do good things without expecting a reward, or do you just say that so you can be seen as a "good person?"</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is your view of the world really so black and white? That what I do can &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; be motivated by selfish desire? That there can't &lt;i&gt;possibly&lt;/i&gt; be any good in me?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">When you have laws &lt;i&gt;against&lt;/i&gt; things like giving food to the homeless and sleeping in your car to avoid driving drunk, you can't tell me the law is "good" -- you can't convince me &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; don't break laws &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; find dumb.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="FourPeopleOverpowering" />
                <state img="#-threatening.png" font-size="small">Sure, the fourth wall may protect you from &lt;i&gt;us&lt;/i&gt;, but remember this the next time you're outnumbered. Remember how easily the people around you could turn on you and pretend it's "the right thing to do."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="RootOfAllEvil" />
                <state img="#-arm.png">Clearly, people who say that have never heard of the sick and twisted things I do free of charge!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">It's like they've never read a history book. Most of the deadliest wars in history had nothing to do with money.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you even know how many murderers killed not for money, but to see if they could get away with it? Or for the rush they'd get? Or out of good ol' fashioned &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Try telling that to a homeless person and see how true it feels, after you go home to your dry bed and fridge full of food.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">A majority of people who express anti-capitalistic sentiments wouldn't last a &lt;i&gt;week&lt;/i&gt; without their purchased creature comforts, let alone growing their own food and sewing their own clothes.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Sure, sure, people who torture animals are just trying to get money out of said animals. That &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; makes sense.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I get it's not meant to be &lt;i&gt;literal&lt;/i&gt;, but it's still a pretty small-minded view.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I mean, don't get me wrong, corporations &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; terrible, but there's other kinds of evil out there who &lt;i&gt;aren't&lt;/i&gt; after your wallet. Case in point: &lt;i&gt;Me!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="HeckThePolice" />
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">It's a valid sentiment. I mean, I could snap your neck &lt;i&gt;right now&lt;/i&gt; and the only thing a cop could do would be to make me apologize to your corpse.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">If that's how you feel, I wonder if I held a gun to your head, would you still be so dismissive of them?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So, what, do people who think like that just expect the law to uphold itself or something? Or are they just gonna take every bad thing that happens to them on the chin?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">All cops are corrupt, absolutely. Just like all homosexuals are ungodly deviants, and everyone who isn't where I'm from is a dirty savage. You hear how that sounds?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope you realize generalizations like that are the source of racial and sexual persecution, and the exact mindset that lead to World War II.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Fighting discrimination with discrimination. It's so hypocritical it makes me laugh!</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png">All cops are corrupt, just like all homosexuals are godless sinners, and everyone who isn't my race is inferior, &lt;i&gt;and everyone who is wrong can never change their mind and must DIE!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I wonder how many people who say that only say it to be on the "right" side -- to be seen as "good," or just to fit in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="RuinYourDay" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">"Making" someone's year would require something &lt;i&gt;incredibly&lt;/i&gt; significant, but all it'd take is one accident to ruin someone's whole &lt;i&gt;life&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Imagine. You're having the time of your life, enjoying some theme park, and them &lt;i&gt;bam&lt;/i&gt;! Rollar coast accident leaves you paralysed from the waist down!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">All it takes is being in the wrong place at the wrong time, and your whole &lt;i&gt;life&lt;/i&gt; could be ruined.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Doesn't even have to be from something &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; did, your life could be ruined by &lt;i&gt;someone else's&lt;/i&gt; poor decision-making or carelessness or incompetense.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Doesn't even have to happen to you directly. It could happen to a loved one, and impact you by proxy. &lt;i&gt;That's what you get for caring about someone&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">All it takes is one touch of bad luck, one accident, one intrusive thought, and everything starts spiraling out of control.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="YourLifeIsYourOwn" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">How much of what you do is determined by what it would make people think of you? If you could get away with it, how much of a douche would you be?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you use slang because &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; like it, or because it's what everyone else is saying? Are you &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; desperate to fit in?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you waste the gift of free will chasing trends and mindlessly listening to what others "recommend" you watch or listen to? Do you ever notice people subtly turning you into themselves?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Think about it. From the clothes you wear to the words you use, how much of it is for &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; and how much of it is so you can be &lt;i&gt;liked&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you even recognize how much of yourself you surpress for the sake of "acceptance?"</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">"I'm an individual," you say, while believing everything you hear and parroting the same jokes everyone else is saying.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="MonsterArt" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">It's almost like the brains that reach beyond our creative boundaries are also wired to break our &lt;i&gt;moral&lt;/i&gt; boundaries too.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">It's almost like humans are comletely fallible beings prone to acting on dark compulsions.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Best part is, whether you live in blissful ignorance of things or it all comes to light, the offender &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; escapes real consequences! It's a real lose-lose situation!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Memes aren't safe, either! In fact, your favorite memes are &lt;i&gt;extremely&lt;/i&gt; likely to have been created by someone who has or &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; do something terrible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-taunt.png">If you expected something nicer-looking, then you haven't been paying attention to just who the heck I am!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, I'm sorry, did you expect something with butterflies or strawberries or something else cute on it, symbolizing a soft interior under the  rough facade?&lt;/i&gt; It's just underwear, dolts!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Play nice and maybe I'll let a strap slide down -- no, really, I'll do it. Trust me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Be thankful you got both boots and not just one. I guess I'm just in a generous mood!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Congratulations, you got my boots off. Your poker skill is equal to that of me simply coming home.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, sorry, were you hoping I'd say something more interesting while I took off my boots?&lt;/i&gt; Guess I just didn't feel like it. Better luck next time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="22">
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="ArmStory">Nope! I cut them off &lt;i&gt;myself&lt;/i&gt;! Well, my sister did it for me, 'cause y'know, &lt;i&gt;arms&lt;/i&gt;, but it was my idea! I couldn't resist giving myself mechanical arms filled with evil technology!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="ArmStory">Nope! I &lt;i&gt;asked&lt;/i&gt; for them to be cut off! Metal arms make me &lt;i&gt;so much&lt;/i&gt; more evil!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Well, maybe I'll just keep you guessing! I don't owe you my backstory!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Maybe I'll just make you keep guessing until you get it right. There's only, like, &lt;i&gt;a thousand&lt;/i&gt; ways to remove someone's arms!</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png" marker="ArmStory">Listen here: Being evil? &lt;i&gt;My&lt;/i&gt; choice. These arms? &lt;i&gt;My&lt;/i&gt; choice. Not getting my overbite corrected? &lt;i&gt;My&lt;/i&gt; choice. &lt;i&gt;Nothing&lt;/i&gt; about me is an accident, got it?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Sometimes the truth is greater than fiction. Sometimes life disappoints. One of those applies to the story about my arms, but I won't tell you which!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">What am I, some kind of cheesy movie villain who exposits her backstory to every opponent she faces? Get real!</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png" marker="ArmStory">It was no accident! It was a &lt;i&gt;decision&lt;/i&gt;! A step towards becoming a better villain! Who knows what body part I might lob off next!</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Why focus on the past when I can tell you your future. Spoilers, it involves me kicking your butts.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="ArmStory">Nah, I cut 'em off, plain and simple.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, I'm sorry, am I expositing too much for you, ~player~?&lt;/i&gt; Guess I'll just leave it there.</state>
                <state img="#-threatening.png" marker="ArmStory">I cut them off to become a better villain! Let that be a lesson: I will stop at &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; to get what I want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="2">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I can't exactly do my villain business in lingerie -- and yes, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; have villain business to attend to when we're done.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" font-size="small">Oh? Did you expect me to take off my stockings first? Nuh uh! Outter layers first, &lt;i&gt;then&lt;/i&gt; underwear! Stockings are worn under shoes, so that makes them underwear! I am very particular about this distinction!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">That's right, I don't wear shorts under my skirt. Like I care if anyone sees up my skirt, it just means I get to punch 'em for being a perv!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-taunt.png">So there. And I'm not gonna &lt;i&gt;stop&lt;/i&gt; cheating, ether! You're gonna have to &lt;i&gt;earn&lt;/i&gt; my crotch!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Leaving in the middle of a strip poker match would &lt;i&gt;hardly&lt;/i&gt; be a fun way to screw with you, anyway. Like, &lt;i&gt;"oh no, you didn't get to see my genitals, just like you do with a majority of the people you meet in life. How clever."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">Count yourself lucky I put my evil tech in my &lt;i&gt;arms&lt;/i&gt; and not my &lt;i&gt;boobs&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">You can touch them, if you want -- as long as you can trust that this isn't just a trick to bring your arms into wrist-breaking range.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, I'm sorry, were you expected pierced nipples?&lt;/i&gt; Way to undermine the self-expressionism of punk culture by expecting every punk to follow the exact same trends, &lt;i&gt;moron&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, were you expected pierced nipples?&lt;/i&gt; Sorry I'm not a porn stereotype, &lt;i&gt;ignoramus&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-taunt.png">You think even for a second that I'm ashamed to be nude? Like, seriously? Really? &lt;i&gt;Me?&lt;/i&gt; Yeah right!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">The sight of nudity obviously makes most people happy, but it makes some people uncomfortable too, so naturally I gotta have that ready as a tool in my arsenal.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">If you didn't believe that my hair was &lt;i&gt;naturally&lt;/i&gt; pink before, I've just proven my case beyond reasonable doubt.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">With a body like &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;, how can anyone call me a "freak?"</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I know, I know. "Kol mamnou' marghoub." Too bad for you, that proverb is true!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I'm sure you were hoping this'd be the part where I start freaking out 'cause I'm out of clothes and I might totally embarrass myself, but too bad, I have too much confidence for that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you're a foot-fetishist, I'll gladly give you a close look at my feet in the form of a swift kick to the face!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">If you think a footjob from me would be better than a handjob, you're overestimating how gentle I'd be with my feet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" priority="0">
                <condition count="1-" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-arm.png">May I remind you to never stick your dick in crazy -- and no, you &lt;i&gt;can't&lt;/i&gt; fix me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Adrien_Costume1">Hey, pal, you know the whole catsuit thing is only cute when &lt;i&gt;girls&lt;/i&gt; do it, right? On you, it just looks like you lost a bet.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Adrien_Costume1">Hey, bub, didn'tcha get the memo? You're supposed to dress as something &lt;i&gt;frightening&lt;/i&gt;. No goon worth anything is gonna be intimidated by &lt;i&gt;Cat Man&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="Adrien_Costume1">... Oh, I get it, you're a cat so you disarm people with cuteness, right? Too bad for you, I'm a dog person!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Adrien_Costume1">Pffft! If your goal with the cat costume was to get your opponents to laugh themselves to death, it's working!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Adrien_Costume1">Listen, bud, there was only one male-identifying individual who could make a cat-themed hero work, and he's dead. So what's that mean for &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kool-aid" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Well, if I'm gonna be stuck in a match with a freakin' mascot, at least it's the one known for breaking through walls...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Well, at least you're not one of those &lt;i&gt;furry&lt;/i&gt; mascots... </state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">I wanna make a joke like "If I get thirsty during the match, I can at least knock you over and take a drink," but actually, I hate sugary drinks.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">I wanna make a joke like "If I get thirsty during the match, I can at least knock you over and take a drink," but actually, I hate sugary drinks, so that joke is inaccurate. Also, if I actually &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; get thirsty, I'm screwed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="mister_clean" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">This guy's like the total opposite of me: Tall, buff, bald guy obsessed with cleaning... Obviously, I hate him.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You like to keep things clean, huh? I bet I could make a mess so big even &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; can't clean it all up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="el_shaggy_blanco" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't care how strong or fast or &lt;i&gt;whatever&lt;/i&gt; this guy is, he won't last a minute against me!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Blanco, huh? Is that supposed to be your power level or something? Just wait until I show you the power of &lt;i&gt;pink&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Tonto ebrio, puede que haya sido poderoso una vez, pero carece de poder de permanencia! Oh? Didn't think I could speak Spanish? Te lo dije, soy una persona de pueblo!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="gay_spaghetti_chef" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">This character greatly offends me! Pasta is &lt;i&gt;garbage&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, really? &lt;i&gt;This guy&lt;/i&gt; had to be here? I cannot &lt;i&gt;possibly&lt;/i&gt; understate just how much I &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; pasta, and anyone who cooks it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="glass_joe" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Aw man, I &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; Punch-Out! Hey, Joe, wanna go toe-to-toe?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Aw man, I &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; Punch-Out! You have &lt;i&gt;no idea&lt;/i&gt; how many times I've knocked out the virtual you, Joe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="astolfo_bean_plushie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">So... am I supposed to be &lt;i&gt;afraid&lt;/i&gt; of this plush or something? 'Cause I can't be afraid of anything that's at the perfect football kick height.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Am I supposed to be offended by this plush calling me gay and implying I have a dick despite &lt;i&gt;clearly&lt;/i&gt; being a cute girl? 'Cause it just looks like a sad attempt at trolling to me.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">... Is this plush gonna try to get us to kill each other or something? Does it realize we're not even trapped here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kamina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Hey, I've heard of you. You're that guy, uh... Super, uh... Ultimate... Hang on, it'll come to me...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Wait wait, I know you, you're... not Ultimate Ronin... not Flamebringer Extreme... uh... can't be Rocketpunch Tanaka... Justice Blade Plus Ultra...?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Lemme see if I can guess your backstory: You never knew your parents. You lost your childhood friend, and now refuse to ever lose a friend again, while also setting out to be the best &lt;i&gt;whatever&lt;/i&gt;  you said you'd be. Am I right? I bet I am!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">I hope you have some &lt;i&gt;actual&lt;/i&gt; powers, 'cause it just isn't fun beatin' up fools who think courage, determination, and a sword are all they need to dish out justice anymore...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="chazz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">You know that Yu-Gi-Oh is just a rip-off of Magic: The Gathering, right? If you want me to take you seriously, play &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; instead.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">&lt;i&gt;Finally&lt;/i&gt;, a card-based something-or-other that doesn't just use Tarot or French-print cards...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Yu-Gi-Oh was much cooler back when it was about various games and not just the Magic rip-off...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Cards? Pass. Anyone still play Dungeon Dice Monsters, though?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="shou_tucker" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" font-size="small">I know I'm supposed to have something real mean to say to this guy, and mean things are my thing, but... I really don't care. So he killed a dog and a daughter for status, big whoop. Not like he committed genocide or something!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">I'm sure you want me to say something extra mean to this guy, but... it's not even worth it. Not like I have the moral high-ground here, anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So this guy killed his dog and his daughter. Big whoop. Do you know how many people I know who've done far worse things &lt;i&gt;for fun&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">So this guy killed his dog and his daughter. Why should I care? What do I look like? &lt;i&gt;Batman?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So this guy killed his dog and his daughter. Am I supposed to care? Do I even need to tell you how that could've been worse?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You expect me to hate this guy? Do I even need to explain how I'm worse than him?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Oh, you think &lt;i&gt;this guy's&lt;/i&gt; the worst? Don't study history, then. You'll quickly find out just how much more awful a human can be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="scm" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png" marker="SCM_Grapple1">&lt;i&gt;Suction cups?&lt;/i&gt; How primitive! Get with the times, loser! Grapple arms are where it's at!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="SCM_Grapple1">Suction Cup Man? Geez, and I thought Kite Man was the pinnacle of lame...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="death" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Death_Cheat1">Oh good, I was getting tired of simply &lt;i&gt;cheating&lt;/i&gt; death. Now I can beat him outright!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">"Bobobo" is a stupid name. It &lt;i&gt;feels&lt;/i&gt; stupid coming out of my mouth. I'm just gonna call you "Bo."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="mama_shotgun" role="target" character="aella" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Nice arm. Bet it doesn't compare to mine, though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="92">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="1" sayingMarker="muststrip_1_magma_speech" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="MG_Speech1">... Alright, fair enough, we &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; use more land. Tides &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; rising...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="96">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="1" sayingMarker="water_speech_0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="AG_Speech1">Not like I have much of a choice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aella" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Tall, blonde, wearing blue... You that "Blue Paladin" I keep hearing about?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You must be Blue Paladin. I was expecting your armor to be more... modern.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="joey" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">You must be Ace, the Wonder Clown. Nice try, but I don't have coulrophobia!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Y'know, believe it or not, I've never met an evil clown -- and keep good tabs on fellow villains! Unless &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; evil?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ribbon_girl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, those arms better be your only power. I am &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; dealing with another singing-power hero today...</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Are those arms your only power? If so, you just met your superior!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="natsuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, did you dye your hair pink 'cause of me? Are you like my biggest fan or something?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hey shortie, you oughta let your hair down like mine. The messy look is &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; better than... whatever you call &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, do yourself a favor and let your hair down, those pins make your bangs look like big nostrils.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm, making jokes about how much you look like a child would be too easy... Says more about the people who're into you than it does you yourself, anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Oh look, it's the me from the universe where I &lt;i&gt;didn't&lt;/i&gt; build myself super rad robot arms.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh. You look kinda like I did before my design was adjusted...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">You that "Magey Maggie" I keep hearing about? Can you teach me some magic or is it just "in your blood?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="104">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Meia_Hair1">You probably get this a lot, but what's up with your hair? Did you go to one of those avant-garde hair stylists? You should ask for your money back.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Meia_Hair1">Your hair is weird. It's like, messy, but still orderly. Do you wake up every morning and comb it into that specific pattern?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="orendi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I know a being of chaos when I see one! You and I are gonna get along just fine, Fourarms!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Ahahaha! A &lt;i&gt;ladybug&lt;/i&gt;? That's the best you got? Do you even have any powers, or are you just some chick in a silly suit?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I know there are a lot of bug-themed heroes, but are there seriously so many of you that a &lt;i&gt;ladybug&lt;/i&gt; was the best you could do?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Pffft, &lt;i&gt;sure&lt;/i&gt;, a &lt;i&gt;ladybug&lt;/i&gt; hero. What next, &lt;i&gt;Phasmid Man&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh, I hate spiders... You'd better not have a spider-face under that hood!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh, I hate spiders... If you have &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; resemblance to a spider, I'm out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="uravity" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Ooh-ravity? Yoo-ravity? &lt;i&gt;Uh-ravity? Ur-avity?&lt;/i&gt; How the heck do you say it? Whatever. Clearly, you need a name-change.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Judging by your name, I take it you've got gravity powers? What, do you make people heavier or something? Not gonna work with me, you can't make flames heavier!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="starfire" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-cute.png">"Starfire," huh? Well, at least &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; of those things is a thing I enjoy. Guess which!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Wait, did you say your name is &lt;i&gt;"Coriander?"&lt;/i&gt; As in, Chinese parsley? What, are you gonna spice me into submission or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I know that walk. You don't have legs. I can get ya some robotic ones, but only on one condition: You use them for evil.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You got fake legs, huh? I can tell. My sister lost her legs too. Surprised you're not using better legs. Crappy ones like whatever &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; got weren't good enough for Griz, they shouldn't be for you either!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can tell by the way you walk, you're walking on fakes. You should get better ones. There's all kinds of cool crap you can cram in that space.</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">Nice fake legs. &lt;i&gt;Not.&lt;/i&gt; You oughta get robotic ones -- or better yet, get robotic &lt;i&gt;arms&lt;/i&gt;, they're crazy rad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="galatea" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Are you the statue that got John Linnell high, or we just playing with some statue for no reason?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="zenobia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Ha! Patrolling the beach, kicking down sandcastles. Classic villainy!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hey, just so you know, once you get your sandcastle done, I'ma kick it down. It's more fun to kick it down when you build it with the express purpose of being kick-proof!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Am I about to be the beach bully who kicks down sandcastles? Yes. Yes I am.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let it be known that I am not above simple beach bullying. I'll kick down a sandcastle at the drop of a hat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="derpy_hooves" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Muffins...? So you got muffin powers? What, do you turn people into muffins or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Shantae_Genie1">Oh man, a &lt;i&gt;genie&lt;/i&gt;? Sweet! Three wishes!... But honestly, I dunno what I'd wish for. My life's great!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Shantae_Genie1">Oh man! Genies are the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt;! Nothing better than making someone regret getting exactly what they wished for!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="beatrix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-rope.png">Ah! Finally, a doctor who gets me! Cybernetics are just the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, if it isn't the &lt;i&gt;coolest&lt;/i&gt; doctor I've ever seen! I know who I'm callin' next time I need some shots!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">&lt;i&gt;Please&lt;/i&gt; tell me you use that arm to forcefully immunize anti-vaccine &lt;i&gt;idiots&lt;/i&gt;! That's my freakin' &lt;i&gt;dream&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="moon" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-humored.png">You're the one everyone hates, huh? Guess that makes you my best friend!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I hear everyone hates you. You know what that earns you? My eternal and unwavering support!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="default-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, aren't you one of the chicks from that Mioda girl's former band, or am I thinking of some other all-girl band that has band practice at tea time?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">A character made with the lowest amount of effort possible? &lt;i&gt;Why?&lt;/i&gt; Everybody knows it's funny to pour mass amounts of energy into the dumbest thing you can think of!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="palutena" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">A &lt;i&gt;literal&lt;/i&gt; goddess, huh? Guess it's time to become a JRPG protagonist, 'cause I'm totally gonna kick this goddess's butt!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="7">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="mia" stage="0" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="franziska" stage="0" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You're a lawyer, huh? Defense or prosecution? Because with me on trial, your job is either going to be a total breeze or the biggest battle of your &lt;i&gt;life&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="panty" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-humored.png">Pffft! &lt;i&gt;"Panty?"&lt;/i&gt; Seriously? That's the dumbest name I've ever heard! That's not even a good &lt;i&gt;stripper&lt;/i&gt; name!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Geez, and I thought "Nero Forte" was a dumb name! Congratulations, "Panty," yours takes the cake!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="erufuda" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">An elf, huh? What kinds of powers do elves have? More than just good hearing, I hope!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Taking a break from making toys, eh? That's a Christmas joke, if you didn't catch it.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Fat jokes are too easy. I gotta think up some elf disses... which... are gonna be much harder, apparently, but much more worthwhile as a result!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="lyn" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Wait a minute, don't tell me &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; are the "Ultimate Ronin" I heard about? I was told that was a guy, and that he dresses like a cowboy... shame on me for believing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; part, I guess...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="kizuna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">AI...? Huh... Now that I think about it, I've &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; met a rogue AI. I know evil robots, but not evil AI. Isn't that &lt;i&gt;weird&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="misty_hgss" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you... Do you just walk around in a swimsuit everywhere you go? I mean, you clearly love swimming, but do you have to make it so obvious?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You... &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; know you can wear swimsuits under &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;, right? You don't have to walk around everywhere like that.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Do you like making it obvious that you're a swimmer, or do you just like showing off your legs?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="73">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="Revy_Guns1">You think you're hot stuff just 'cause you're good with guns? How much good do you think they'll do against someone like me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="saki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Saki_Issues1">Hey, did I hear you say something about you having father issues? &lt;i&gt;Gee, sure does make me happy to have a loving, supportive father who has never wronged me!&lt;/i&gt; Ahaha hahaha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="CD_Ice1">Pretty smart of you going rocker instead of hero. If ice is all you got, you're not going far!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="constanze" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">So you don't talk? &lt;i&gt;At all&lt;/i&gt;? Great. It's like dealing with a mime, except somehow sadder...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dreamcatcher" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Prison1">So you broke out of prison, huh? Am I supposed to be impressed? I've done that too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dreamcatcher" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Good1">With powers like yours, why bother being on the side of good? You could do whatever you want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Oh great, here comes the exposition...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="106">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Jura_Beauty1">So I'm supposed to be impressed with you just 'cause you have silky hair and big boobs? Like there aren't literally &lt;i&gt;billions&lt;/i&gt; of other women like that alive right now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="turandot" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Turandot_Dating1">No joke, I respect what you do. Cutting through all the bullcrap and "games" that come with dating. And if a few hundred fools fall in a spike pit in the process, that's not your problem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="Helperchan_Helpful1">Would you stop being so helpful all the time? You're making my job harder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Helperchan_WhyHelp1">Why are you so eager to be helpful, anyway? Overcompensating for something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="85">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Meia_EatingBabies1">Y'know, I'm surprised people are cool with you playing here, considering Mejarians eat their own children.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="86">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Jura_GrayHair1">By the way, you know there's like a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; noticeable gray hair hanging down, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="88">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Caitlin_Psychic1">Am I supposed to be &lt;i&gt;impressed&lt;/i&gt; that you're psychic? I've seen &lt;i&gt;lots&lt;/i&gt; of psychic super heroes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="89">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Caitlin_Weak1">So you know people think you're the weakest member of the Elite Four, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="AG_Aspirations1">Don't you have bigger aspirations than to dress like a waiter at some cheesy theme restaurant and do &lt;i&gt;someone elses'&lt;/i&gt; bidding?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="MG_Weapons1">So this is all you are? Some grunt? Did your boss at least give you illegal weapons or anything like that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="101">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="AG_WaterWeak1">Gotta say, pretty brave of you to use a type as weak as Water. I mean, I could take one out &lt;i&gt;myself&lt;/i&gt; with one little zap from my built-in taser, yet you use them anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="102">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="MG_FireWeak1">Gotta say, pretty brave of you to use a type as weak as Fire. I mean, I could beat them myself with a decent fire extinguisher, but you use them anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="109">
                <condition role="target" character="nadeshiko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Nadeshiko_Locations1">You &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; realize you've based your whole personality on just being outside, right? Like, imagine if &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; based my whole personality around being in an arcade all the time. Don't you think that's weird?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="raven" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Funny, I know a guy named Raven. You... wouldn't happen to know him, would you?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Aw man, I totally forgot "Raven" is a gender-neutral name... Thought I was gonna be playing against Raven von Grimblade...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="rin" />
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Ahahaha! You don't got &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; arms! And here I am with my crazy rad &lt;i&gt;robotic&lt;/i&gt; ones!</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">Hey, how come you don't have robotic arms? You know they come with all kinds of rad stuff now, right? Check &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; out!</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Hey armless chick, isn't it funny how I could punch you from a mile away, and you couldn't punch back if I were right up in your face?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-disgust.png">A tie? Ugh! You'd think it'd mean &lt;i&gt;twice&lt;/i&gt; the pain, but it just means no pain at all -- except for me, who enjoys seeing people lose!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Wow. You beat me, kept the game going, and then got a tie! The odds of that must be pretty low!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="25">
                <state img="#-humored.png">What a boring pick! I unironically love it!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Could you possibly strip any less? No seriously, could you? That be a good thing for me to know!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">&lt;i&gt;Yes!&lt;/i&gt; The lamest ~clothing.ifPlural(things|thing)~ possible! A complete waste of everyone's time! Disappointment incarnate!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Aho ni toriau naka -- I just called you a fool in Japanese!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Is that all? Ce nest pas la mer  boire!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can't get mad at that -- quite literally. My pettiness has basically died.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">~clothing.ifPlural(The fact that you still have those surprises me more than you taking off &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; them|The fact that you still have that surprises me more than you taking off &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; that.)~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm just here to annoy people, so if you wanna keep doing that, I won't complain.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Mmm, feel that sweet, sweet disappointment!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Don't you just &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; the sound of people not getting what they want?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Doesn't matter how long you stall, anyway. Time will run out for you, just as it always does for my opponents.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Krummes Holz gibt auch gerades Feuer. That's one of my favorite German sayings -- it's about fire.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">"Il ny a pas de quoi fouetter un chat," as the French say. Well, I might just whip you anyway!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Feeling, uh... lighter, or whatever?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh. Moves like &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; are probably how I lost despite cheating.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If I had played more like that, I'd probably still be evil right now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="97">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="1" saidMarker="water_speech_1_stop_humans" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="AG_Speech2a">You're going to accelerate climate change? What is this, a Saturday morning cartoon?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="98">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="1" saidMarker="water_speech_1_bring_balance" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="AG_Speech2b">So... you're accelerating the world's flooding to combat ocean litter? That's like combating graffiti by just &lt;i&gt;building more walls.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="93">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="MG_Speech2">I already said it was a fine idea! What're you gonna do about it, though? It's one thing to &lt;i&gt;talk&lt;/i&gt; about it, so why don't you &lt;i&gt;do it&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-humored.png">What a boring pick! I unironically love it!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Could you possibly strip any less? No seriously, could you? That be a good thing for me to know!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">&lt;i&gt;Yes!&lt;/i&gt; The lamest ~clothing.ifPlural(things|thing)~ possible! A complete waste of everyone's time! Disappointment incarnate!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Aho ni toriau naka -- I just called you a fool in Japanese!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Is that all? Ce nest pas la mer  boire!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can't get mad at that -- quite literally. My pettiness has basically died.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">~clothing.ifPlural(The fact that you still have those surprises me more than you taking off &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; them|The fact that you still have that surprises me more than you taking off &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; that.)~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="94">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="2" saidMarker="mg_strip_shoes_take_back_land" sayingMarker="mg_strip_shoes_take_back_land_after" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="MG_Speech3a">Oh, I see. Your group's all false promises, no action. Typical.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="95">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="2" saidMarker="mg_strip_shoes_who_needs_water" sayingMarker="mg_strip_shoes_who_needs_water_after" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="MG_Speech3b">&lt;i&gt;That's it?&lt;/i&gt; You're doing this 'cause you're scared of some fish? What next, you're gonna eradicate darkness 'cause you're tired of sleeping with a nightlight?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="100">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="2" saidMarker="water_speech_1_stop_humans" sayingMarker="water_speech_2_stop_humans" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="AG_Speech3a">Oh, I see, &lt;i&gt;you're delusional&lt;/i&gt; -- or at the very least extremely ignorant of actual climate change issues.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="99">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="2" saidMarker="water_speech_1_bring_balance" sayingMarker="water_speech_2_bring_balance" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="AG_Speech3b">&lt;i&gt;Oh yeah, sure, flood the world because some guy told you to.&lt;/i&gt; Real good critical thinking you've done there, Grunt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm just here to annoy people, so if you wanna keep doing that, I won't complain.</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Mmm, feel that sweet, sweet disappointment!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Don't you just &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; the sound of people not getting what they want?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Doesn't matter how long you stall, anyway. Time will run out for you, just as it always does for my opponents.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Krummes Holz gibt auch gerades Feuer. That's one of my favorite German sayings -- it's about fire.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">"Il ny a pas de quoi fouetter un chat," as the French say. Well, I might just whip you anyway!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Feeling, uh... lighter, or whatever?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Huh. Moves like &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; are probably how I lost despite cheating.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If I had played more like that, I'd probably still be evil right now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7" id="26">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Gosh, your sense of fashion is so noteworthy! I should start dressing more like you! &lt;i&gt;Not!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I knew you'd go for ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~. Could you possibly &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt; any easier to predict?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">A basic move from a basic individual.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Oh yeah, make it nice and slow for me. Draw it out as long as possible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="39">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if I should change up my wardrobe. I'll have to consider if I still like the punk look...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7" id="27">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I would say "~clothing.ifPlural(Those look better on the floor than they did on you|That looks better on the floor than it did on you)~," but that could be interpreted as a complement to &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, not &lt;i&gt;the floor&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">If you couldn't tell from my own choice in clothes, I have enough of an eye for fashion to say for sure that &lt;i&gt;yours&lt;/i&gt; is legally blind, so this is an improvement.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Like I care about your fashion sense! I'm the &lt;i&gt;last&lt;/i&gt; person who'd take fashion advice from anyone, let alone from &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Das ist mir Wurst! Or in English, "Your whole outfit sucks, anyway!"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Did I tell you earlier that I think your outfit's bad? B-because I don't mean it anymore.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" saidMarker="Natasha_Ice1" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="CD_Ice2">Finally, a super-person who knows their place! None of that "I'll find a way" hero crap!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dreamcatcher" stage="0" saidMarker="Natasha_Prison1" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Prison2">Guess I'll just have to take your word for it. So what do these "dream powers" do, anyway? They sound totally useless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="69">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="0" sayingMarker="Stripping_RuneslayerFakeout" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Helperchan_XevozFakeout1">Don't listen to hear. She's just spouting Xevoz lore -- and not even purely canonical stuff.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="1" saidMarker="Natasha_Helpful1" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" marker="Helperchan_Helpful2">Maybe not &lt;i&gt;directly&lt;/i&gt;, but everyone needs someone to hate -- it's gotta go &lt;i&gt;somewhere&lt;/i&gt;, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="66">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png">So basically the opposite of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Gosh, your sense of fashion is so noteworthy! I should start dressing more like you! &lt;i&gt;Not!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I knew you'd go for ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~. Could you possibly &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt; any easier to predict?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">A basic move from a basic individual.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Oh yeah, make it nice and slow for me. Draw it out as long as possible!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if I should change up my wardrobe. I'll have to consider if I still like the punk look...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="1" saidMarker="Stripping_RuneslayerFakeout" sayingMarker="Natasha_XevozFakeout1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helperchan_XevozFakeout1" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" marker="Helperchan_XevozFakeout2">It's what I do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="63">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="2" saidMarker="Natasha_Helpful2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helperchan_Helpful2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Helperchan_Helpful3">If that really worked, I wouldn't here! Nor would any other villain!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="1" saidMarker="Natasha_Ice2" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="CD_Ice3">If more people thought like you, my job would be a whole lot easier!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dreamcatcher" stage="1" saidMarker="Natasha_Prison2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Prison3" font-size="small">Hmm, that power would allow you to easily neutralize enemies by exploiting their desires and fears. And if you can create whatever you want, you have effectively limitless direct combat potential. Alright, I take back what I said, &lt;i&gt;for now&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="67">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">She's not even getting paid to be here, she's just some creepy weirdo who won't stop coming here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I would say "~clothing.ifPlural(Those look better on the floor than they did on you|That looks better on the floor than it did on you)~," but that could be interpreted as a complement to &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;, not &lt;i&gt;the floor&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">If you couldn't tell from my own choice in clothes, I have enough of an eye for fashion to say for sure that &lt;i&gt;yours&lt;/i&gt; is legally blind, so this is an improvement.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Like I care about your fashion sense! I'm the &lt;i&gt;last&lt;/i&gt; person who'd take fashion advice from anyone, let alone from &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Das ist mir Wurst! Or in English, "Your whole outfit sucks, anyway!"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Did I tell you earlier that I think your outfit's bad? B-because I don't mean it anymore.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7" id="28">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Told ya it was only a matter of time until you had to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">I knew we'd bleed you dry -- be glad I'm not &lt;i&gt;literally&lt;/i&gt; bleeding you dry! You wouldn't have been the first!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Too bad you didn't take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off sooner. I would've had &lt;i&gt;a bit&lt;/i&gt; more respect for you, but you squandered your opportunity.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Comme on fait son lit, on se couche. That's French for "Do it already!"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="40">
                <state img="#-cute.png">C'mon, you got this! I-I'm sure you know that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7" id="29">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sure hope you don't start getting cold! Wouldn't want you getting sick or something! &lt;i&gt;No, really, I mean it.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">How's it feel, running out of viable moves?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Can you feel everyone's eyes on your skin? Well maybe they care less than you think.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Waqtuk fi hadhih alluebat yanfud biqadr ahtimami biki.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="41">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">See, it's just like... well, &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; you're used to. I guess I still don't know you all that well...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="3" saidMarker="Natasha_WhyHelp1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helperchan_WhyHelp1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Helperchan_WhyHelp2">Really? Nothing? I don't believe it. You're compensating for a lack of friends, or a bad home life, or &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt;, I just know it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dreamcatcher" stage="1" saidMarker="Natasha_Good1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Good2">I don't see the difference. You got out of Lucid Lockdown, what makes Cloudcracker so hard?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Told ya it was only a matter of time until you had to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">I knew we'd bleed you dry -- be glad I'm not &lt;i&gt;literally&lt;/i&gt; bleeding you dry! You wouldn't have been the first!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Too bad you didn't take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off sooner. I would've had &lt;i&gt;a bit&lt;/i&gt; more respect for you, but you squandered your opportunity.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Comme on fait son lit, on se couche. That's French for "Do it already!"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-cute.png">C'mon, you got this! I-I'm sure you know that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9" id="80">
                <condition status="not_naked" role="self" />
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="5" sayingMarker="Natasha_GoingDown" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="Helperchan_GoingDown">Bring it on, nerd!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="81">
                <condition role="target" character="helper-chan" stage="4" saidMarker="Natasha_WhyHelp2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Helperchan_WhyHelp2" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="Helperchan_WhyHelp3">Oh, I see, it's a sexual thing, then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dreamcatcher" stage="2" saidMarker="Natasha_Good2" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="Dreamcatcher_Good3">Okay, &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt; I see your point. I'll have to be &lt;i&gt;extra&lt;/i&gt; careful around these "Skylander" guys, then...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sure hope you don't start getting cold! Wouldn't want you getting sick or something! &lt;i&gt;No, really, I mean it.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">How's it feel, running out of viable moves?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Can you feel everyone's eyes on your skin? Well maybe they care less than you think.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Waqtuk fi hadhih alluebat yanfud biqadr ahtimami biki.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">See, it's just like... well, &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; you're used to. I guess I still don't know you all that well...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="30">
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="452">Sure, sure, flaunt your chest. Not like &lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; confident super person doesn't already do that.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="453">Oh yes, everybody &lt;i&gt;loves&lt;/i&gt; when the hero's shirt gets ripped off in the heat of battle. &lt;i&gt;Not.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="454">Tell me you &lt;i&gt;at least&lt;/i&gt; got some scars goin' on under there? Make it &lt;i&gt;interesting&lt;/i&gt; for me.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="455">Now's the part where you reveal gang tattoos, right? &lt;i&gt;If only!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="42">
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Wow, a guy taking off his ~clothing~ when I'm actually in the mind to appreciate it? How wonderful.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="english" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="671">Oh good, no big, gaudy Union Jack tattoo. You've at least got &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; going for ya.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="31">
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="389">I hope you don't expect me to care about the sight of your chest. Do you &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; how many dudes in tight spandex I see on a regular basis?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="390">I can at least appreciate that your outfit actually &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt; ~clothing.ifPlural(some|a)~ ~clothing~. You ever see those costumes that are &lt;i&gt;designed&lt;/i&gt; to be shirtless? They're &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; tacky!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="391">&lt;i&gt;Ooh, male nipples. I'm so excited. Not!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="392">Doesn't matter how fit or flabby your chest is, a punch to the gut with an electrified metal fist will still put ya on the ground!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="43">
                <state img="#-arm.png">Too bad I don't have much of a sense of touch in my hands...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="969">Don't expect any weight jokes from me, by the way. Your size and shape doesn't make me hate you any more or less than anyone else.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="1010">I, for one, &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; your larger physique. It's more mass for you to throw around if you decide to get violent.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="32">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="285">Do you want me to mock your dick &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt; or wait 'til I actually see it?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="286">You can keep ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ on if you want. I can kick you in the dick later either way!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="287">Yep, that's just how it goes. Men can't keep their ~clothing~ on around me. I'm too hot for my own good.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="288">I've had heroes try to seduce me before. Never works. Always funny, though!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="44">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is there even any way you can take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off in a way that doesn't just have it all fall out like a drunk out of a bar? I-I'm having a hard time imagining one.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="19">Nope, I'm not sayin' &lt;i&gt;a thing&lt;/i&gt; about your dick until I can confirm whether or not you're into humiliation. Wouldn't wanna point and laugh if you're &lt;i&gt;into it&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="20">My desire to not give you what you want is stronger than my desire to mock you, so don't expect any insults from me until I know you're not into that.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="21">... Dang it, not saying anything at all could be seen as an acknowledgment of how small your dick is, which you &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; be into. This is harder than I thought...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="22">Encouragement, humiliation... Crap, there's got to be &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; avenue I can take here that's universally insulting...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">A-are you into size-shaming? I might still have enough mean left in me for that, if you actually &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; it.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I'm sorry, but even in my right mind, I don't have anything nice to say about that.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; shouldn't touch that with these hands. There's an &lt;i&gt;immense&lt;/i&gt; risk of completely destroying it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="42">Tell me you're one'a those guys who likes to get their dick step on and stuff! I'll give you a kick to the nuts right now, into it or not!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="43">In case you couldn't already guess, a handjob from me would be awful, so don't even ask. If you want me to literally ruin your dick, just ask for &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; instead!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="44">What? You think 'cause I got an overbite that I can't give a good blowjob? I will prove you wrong just to spite you and your tooth hate!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="45">It's not just me who thinks penises look really stupid, right? Like, being evil aside, I'm not the only one who thinks they're just dumb lumps of flesh, right?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="216">Don't you just &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; how "dick" rhymes with "kick," by the way? It's like it was meant to be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-arm.png">It's a good think footjobs are a thing, because... well, it's pretty obvious.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Heh heh. Sorry. I still think penises are kinda funny-looking.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="50">Do you think you're hot stuff just 'cause you got a big dick? How much good does it do for you, anyway? I bet it's less than you think!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="51">Nice dick. Did it come with a sense of sexual entitlement pre-installed, or is that something you picked up on your own?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="52">Hey, when you're bangin' someone, do you actually listen to their needs, or do you just jackhammer them like some dumb jock who thinks it's all about speed?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="53">If "big penis humiliation" isn't already a thing, I'm gonna &lt;i&gt;make it&lt;/i&gt; a thing! Big dicks are dumb and so are the guys who have them!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="900">You ever hear the Arabic proverb "Kllh eind alearab sabun?" Yeah, that's me right now, and &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; the soap -- you don't wanna be the soap.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-arm.png">I'm &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; not touching that. I'd just injury it, and that'd be a shame.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="33">
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="480">I may be an advocate for evil, but I really don't give a crap if women choose to bind their breasts on a daily basis or not.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="481">Well? We already know what size you are, so all you're really revealing to us is your nipples.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="482">Milk sacks. Great. I'm &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; excited.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="483">Ah, so we're gonna see your boobs, then? Ha! &lt;i&gt;Boobs.&lt;/i&gt; What a &lt;i&gt;stupid&lt;/i&gt; word!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1129">Oh, sure, I &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; care about your breasts, &lt;i&gt;if I were still a breastfeeding infant.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="45">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Must actually be pretty nice to finally take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off, huh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="181">Hmm. There's probably &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; dis I could be saying right now. Gimme a sec...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="182">Huh, there really aren't a lot of good disses for small chests that aren't completely trite... I'll have to invent some new ones...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="183">... Crap, thinking up good, unique jeers for small chests is harder than I thought...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="184">... Don't expect me to say anything about your boobs until I can think of an insult about 'em you haven't already heard...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Us bitty titties gotta stick together, r-right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="209">I actually don't have a whole lot of evil things I would do to a pair of breasts. But I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; a genius, so I'll think of more things soon enough.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="208">"Boob" is a pretty apt word for them. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; making an embarrassing mistake by showing them, so therefore, you have thoroughly "boobed."</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="210">Huh. There's not a whole lot of evil you can do with a pair of breasts, is there? Like, teasing is basically it. I can do more evil than that with my &lt;i&gt;foot&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="211">You ever get punched in the tit? I think it's &lt;i&gt;hilarious&lt;/i&gt; when it happens!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1144">Seriously, why would I want to do something as infantile as sucking on a tit? What, am I supposed to sleep in a crib too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="48">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">All natural, huh? S-sorry, I'm just thinking about how many people I know with physical enhancements.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="189">Have those started causing you back aches yet? If not, I can help speed up the process!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="190">I love how much big breasts get in the way of the person who has 'em!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="191">The big boobs of an even bigger boob -- I'm calling you a fool, if you didn't catch that.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="192">Y'know, I'm &lt;i&gt;glad&lt;/i&gt; mine are so small. Helps me stay agile. Watching &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; try to do the things &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; do would be like watching an elephant trying to perform Shakespeare.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="880">You ever hear the Japanese saying "Neko ni koban?" Yeah, that's this right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Is it nice having big breasts? I image they're quite the hassle, but they could have their benefits, right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="pierced_nipples" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="158">Piercings? Crap, that means you &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; pain. I mean, why else would you make it so easy?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="844">Enjoy the mental image of me ripping those piercings right outta your nipples, 'cause that's &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; something I'd do to you!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="845">Pierced nipples, eh? Oh, I see, so you're one of &lt;i&gt;those&lt;/i&gt; people?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="846">Don't go thinking you're "alternative" piercings make you as hardcore as &lt;i&gt;me. You've&lt;/i&gt; got little bits of metal hanging from you, &lt;i&gt;I've&lt;/i&gt; got entirely mechanical arms. We're not the same.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="34">
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="410">I always knew my good looks could get a gal's ~clothing~ off! &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="411">Well then? Drop ~clothing.ifPlural('em|it)~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="412">Know that even if I don't say anything, I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; be heavily judging your grooming.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png" oneShotId="413">You sure you wanna do that yourself? I can rip ~clothing.ifPlural('em|it)~ off from right here! And I do mean &lt;i&gt;rip&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1457">Enjoy this moment, because the anticipation of something is always better than the actual thing -- &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="46">
                <state img="#-confused.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Are those|Is that)~ comfortable at all? It's pretty important to keep things comfortable... down there... and stuff...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="heart_pubes" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1515">A &lt;i&gt;heart shape?&lt;/i&gt; Geez, could you &lt;i&gt;get&lt;/i&gt; any more tacky?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="landing_strip" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1517">So were you &lt;i&gt;trying&lt;/i&gt; to make your pubes look like a bad moustache, or...?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1518">Oh good, I was just hoping your pubes would look like Charlie Chaplin's moustache. &lt;i&gt;Not.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="263">In case you were wondering, &lt;i&gt;no&lt;/i&gt;, my hands &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; have a vibrate function. You don't want these bad girls anywhere &lt;i&gt;near&lt;/i&gt; your crotch!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="264">Ugh, you ever notice how many euphemisms for "vagina" are gross-sounding? And they're all made up by people who supposedly &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; them!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="265">Vaginas are &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; more evil than penises. Penises may be for ramming, but vaginas are for &lt;i&gt;overtaking&lt;/i&gt;, and &lt;i&gt;grabbing&lt;/i&gt; what you want -- i.e., &lt;i&gt;the penis&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="266">You ever think about how much explosives you could pack in there? I mean, it's obviously a bad idea if you intend on &lt;i&gt;watching&lt;/i&gt; the explosion, but do you ever just &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; about it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-rope.png">If I didn't already mention it, these things don't have a vibrate function. I could certainly put that in the next pair, though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1183">You sure there's a vagina under there? I can't see it through all of the freakin' hair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="410">I always knew my good looks could get a gal's ~clothing~ off! &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="411">Well then? Drop ~clothing.ifPlural('em|it)~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="412">Know that even if I don't say anything, I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; be heavily judging your grooming.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png" oneShotId="413">You sure you wanna do that yourself? I can rip ~clothing.ifPlural('em|it)~ off from right here! And I do mean &lt;i&gt;rip&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1457">Enjoy this moment, because the anticipation of something is always better than the actual thing -- &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confused.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Are those|Is that)~ comfortable at all? It's pretty important to keep things comfortable... down there... and stuff...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Hey, just so it's clear, I don't hate you 'cause of your identity or genitals. I'd hate you even if you were a brain in a jar.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Oh look, you have a dick. &lt;i&gt;Guess who still doesn't care.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">Dick or no, my hands will &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; feel terrible down there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="futanari_full_package" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cute.png">Oh good, you have balls. Now I know where to kick!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-arm.png">It's a good think footjobs are a thing, because... well, it's pretty obvious.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">Heh heh. Sorry. I still think penises are kinda funny-looking.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7" id="61" oneShotId="29" priority="900">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Mommy" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Daddy" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="nickname*=Loser">
                    <text>&lt;i&gt;"~player~?"&lt;/i&gt; Nah, I'm not even gonna go there. It's too easy!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="NicknameMommyDaddy" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="62" oneShotId="28" priority="900">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Master" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Mistress" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-taunt-extended.png" marker="nickname*=Minion">
                    <text>&lt;i&gt;"~player~?"&lt;/i&gt; Yeah right! You really think you've got power over me when I've got arms like &lt;i&gt;these&lt;/i&gt;? If anything, &lt;i&gt;I'm your&lt;/i&gt; mistress and &lt;i&gt;you're my&lt;/i&gt; minion -- and there's nothing you can do about it!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="NicknameMasterMistress" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="77" oneShotId="30" priority="899">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NicknameMasterMistress" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Master" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Mistress" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="nickname*=Friend">Oh, I guess now that I'm not evil, you're not my "minion" anymore. What should I call you, then? I'm still not keen on "~player~..." Uh, how about just "Friend?" Hopefully that doesn't sound condescending.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="78" oneShotId="31" priority="899">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NicknameMommyDaddy" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Mommy" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Daddy" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="nickname*=Friend">Hey, uh, sorry about calling you a loser earlier. I still don't wanna call you "~player~," so how about, uh... "Friend?" That's the best I can come up with...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="55">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="scm" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="SCM_Defeated">Let that be a lesson to you all: No hero is too lame for me to defeat for my own amusement!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" character="el_shaggy_blanco" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png">No es tan duro ahora, verdad? Te decepcionas.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Saba que eras una broma desde el principio, pero todava me encuentro decepcionado, lo que solo puede significar que eres una broma &lt;i&gt;sin gracia&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Sumrgete, perdedor!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Oye, has ledo mis burlas, jugador? Si usa una mquina para traducir, eso es hacer trampa!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="not_lost_all" role="target" character="el_shaggy_blanco" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="476">Tu jugada, perdedor!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="477">De verdad hablas espaol o solo eres un farsante?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="478">Eres una broma dbil que solo se debilita con el tiempo!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="479">Quienquiera que te haya invitado no debe haber tenido nada mejor que hacer con su tiempo!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="15" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-cute.png">"I don't know what it is, but there's just something so special about you, ~player~!" &lt;i&gt;Pah!&lt;/i&gt; You really fall for that crap?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Wow, I dunno what it is about you, ~player~, but for some reason, I don't want to be evil to you... &lt;i&gt;Yeah right!&lt;/i&gt; You really fall for crap like that?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You don't really fall for that "there's something special about you that I can't figure out" crap, do you? I mean, c'mon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="8">
                <condition filter="uses_camera" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-arm.png">Oh neat, a photographer. Wanna get a good shot, or can I just skip to the part where I smash your camera?</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">Hey, get a nice photo of me while you can before I turn your camera into a smoldering pile of parts!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Oh man, a photographer! I &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; smashing cameras!</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png">Hey, just so you know, the only way you're getting out of this with your camera in one piece is if you're a photographer for Villains Weekly.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... Grabbing nude photos of us to use for blackmail... I'm not sure if that's a flavor of evil I'm okay with...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="superhero" status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="167">I keep telling you super heroes you're never gonna beat me, but you never listen. Count yourself lucky that &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is your fate. It could've been worse.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="193">You're gettin' off lucky! Last super hero I beat lost some teeth!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="696">Let this be a lesson to you. You can't beat me here, and you &lt;i&gt;definitely&lt;/i&gt; can't beat me out there!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="697">You're not invincible -- don't forget that, &lt;i&gt;"hero."&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="villain" status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="175">I think we just learned who the best villain here is -- not that it was ever in doubt!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="719">Hero, villain, it makes no difference to me. I'll whoop you all the same!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="720">Aw, too bad, I was &lt;i&gt;this close&lt;/i&gt; to asking you to form an alliance with me -- &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="english" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1094" marker="nickname*=Manchester">If you reveal a giant Union Jack tattoo on your chest, I'm out.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="1106" marker="nickname*=Plonker">Oy, mate, I ain't the one who's nutter. &lt;i&gt;You're&lt;/i&gt; the one who's an absolute muppet. &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt; British slang is so dumb! And they say &lt;i&gt;Americans&lt;/i&gt; are the ones who butcher the English language!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="princess" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1463">I hope you're not one of those princesses who fell in love with their rescuer. "White Knight syndrome" is very real and very much bullcrap.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="4" priority="71">
                <condition filter="villain" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make no mistake, just 'cause you're a villain too doesn't mean I'm going to give you any slack. I'm not above thrashing my peers!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="6" priority="71">
                <condition filter="superhero" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Are you one of those super heroes that has dumb names for all of your moves? I swear, if I here another awful move name, I'm gonna barf!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" font-size="small">You better not be one of those heroes that has names for all his moves. Doesn't matter if you call your ice attack "Blinding Blizzard" or "Hail Force Ultra" or &lt;i&gt;whatever&lt;/i&gt;, you're just the same as all the other guys who can shoot ice!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="46">I'll be sure to add your name to my ever-growing list of people I've bested later.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="47">&lt;i&gt;Oh gosh, I'm so surprised you lost. It's not like an evil genius such as myself has a solid grasp on statistics and the analysis of such.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="48">Considering there's a good chance you were &lt;i&gt;hoping&lt;/i&gt; to lose, it's hardly apt to gloat, but I'm gonna do it anyway. &lt;i&gt;Suck it, chump!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="49">You should've known you were gonna lose the moment I showed up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="196">You didn't think you were invincible, did you? Ha! Even people with that as a super power can still be hurt &lt;i&gt;somehow&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="197">The first loss of what I'm sure will be many, &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; losses for you!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="198">It doesn't take a genius to realize how inevitable this was for you.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="199">So, are you gonna see this thing through, or are you gonna run away at the first sign of trouble?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="221">Go ahead, make your move. The first one's always &lt;i&gt;super&lt;/i&gt; easy to see coming!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="47">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="457">Sorry you lost, but not sorry about having to masturbate, I guess?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="471">Shame to lose, but what are ya gonna do? Stuff cards in your mechanical arms? Heh heh...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="472">On the bright side, you outlasted &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;. I was cheating pretty hardcore, so that's something!</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png" oneShotId="473">Hey, I think I see the evil leaving &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; body too! Haha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="5" priority="1">
                <condition status="not_lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Play with fire, you get burned! And as someone who enjoys playing with fire, I can confirm this from experience.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Chop chop, loser! You know the drill!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Nice going. &lt;i&gt;Not.&lt;/i&gt; And yes, I know you got unlucky, but I can still mock you for your card-swapping decisions!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">You're gonna have to try harder than that to beat me at &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;, let alone some dumb card game!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">If whatever ~name~ does makes you fall asleep, I reserve full rights to either slap you awake or leave you asleep and draw stupid stuff on your face!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I really couldn't care less what you decide to take off, given that you're highly likely to take off everything eventually anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">You just gonna stand there and talk or are you gonna get on with it?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Oh, look at that, the cards don't like you either! &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">If you fight as well as you play cards, I could beat you with one arm tied behind my back!</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Ball's in your court, &lt;i&gt;loser&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Don't forget, you're always free to turn tail and run! Won't be as satisfying as beating you, but still embarrassing for you, and therefore still enjoyable for me!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Like taking candy from a baby -- which I have &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; done, by the way. What am I gonna do with candy covered in infant germs?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Wer rastet, der rostet! That's German for "You suck at this!"</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Makeru ga kachi, &lt;i&gt;loser&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png">Jakuniku kyoushoku! &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt; Love that saying.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="6" priority="1">
                <condition status="not_lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">It's hard to believe I cheated, lost, and the game is &lt;i&gt;still going&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, at least now you don't have to worry about me putting pressure on you.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I have a lot more patience now, so just... do whatever.</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">At least we know &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; not cheating. Haha! R-right...?</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Well, you're not out just yet, so... Good luck, or whatever.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I certainly don't have a horse in this race. I guess my horse was &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, and I lost... What a weird thought: "I was my horse..."</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">If you don't want to strip yourself, I could... No. Never mind. That wouldn't be safe...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I don't care what you strip, how you strip it, or... really anything else. Not in an apathetic kind of way, of course, in a relaxed way.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7" id="56">
                <condition role="target" character="scm" stage="0" saidMarker="scm_natasha_workout" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="SCM_Grapple2c">That's the point, &lt;i&gt;genius&lt;/i&gt;. Grappling &lt;i&gt;doesn't&lt;/i&gt; take effort. It saves you time and energy for things that &lt;i&gt;matter&lt;/i&gt;, like defeating your opponents, or, oh I dunno, &lt;i&gt;going to a gym for a proper workout.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="scm" stage="0" saidMarker="scm_natasha_kiteman" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="SCM_Grapple2b">What's lame is that instead of a kite he could be using a jetpack, or a rotor pack, or &lt;i&gt;literally any form of active propulsion&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="scm" stage="0" saidMarker="scm_natasha_grapplegirl" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="SCM_Grapple2a" font-size="small">&lt;i&gt;Oh yeah, sure, there's no adventure to being able to go wherever I want at a moment's notice.&lt;/i&gt; 'Cause I &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; don't have precise control over my grapple function.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="default-chan" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Oh great, she's mute. &lt;i&gt;Fun&lt;/i&gt;. I actually wanted to know what band she was in, too...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="scm" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="SCM_Grapple2d">&lt;i&gt;Yeah, sure, I totally believe you've been to hell.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition gender="male" role="target" layers="4-" startingLayers="4-" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="important" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Well, at least &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; here wants to make this game entertaining!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition gender="female" role="target" layers="5-" startingLayers="5-" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="important" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Well, at least &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; here wants to make this game entertaining!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="98">You ever fill someone's shoes with bees before? It's &lt;i&gt;exactly&lt;/i&gt; as hilarious as it sounds.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="123">Nice shoes. Do they come in &lt;i&gt;normal&lt;/i&gt; sizes?</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="134">Oh good, your shoes! Now it'll be easier to stomp your toes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="mask" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="135">This isn't the first time I've unmasked someone. I got the masks off of a few Order of Heroes dorks. They quit the hero business because of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="sandals" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="152">Aw, too bad, I would've wanted you to wear those more. Sandals are the most dangerous footwear!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="238">Screw you for wearing sandals to begin with. No one wants to see your ugly freakin' toes, that's why &lt;i&gt;shoes&lt;/i&gt; were invented!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="blazer" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="146">Ugh, blazers are so lame. Call me when it's &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; blazing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="thong" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="759">Whoever invented thongs completely failed with them. They're not comfortable, they're &lt;i&gt;barely&lt;/i&gt; functional, and they're not sexy in the slightest!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1436">I can't believe people actually &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; thongs.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="1452">Nice throwback to early 2000s fashion trends. &lt;i&gt;Not!&lt;/i&gt; Thongs are a trend that should've stayed dead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="weapon" />
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png" oneShotId="785">Shouldn't have brought ~clothing.ifPlural(~clothing~|a ~clothing~)~ to a mechanical arm fight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="cape" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="827">Y'know, I always hear people talking about how dangerous capes can be, but I've never actually seen any cape-related accidents -- or &lt;i&gt;caused&lt;/i&gt; any, for that matter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="armor" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="998">Oh yeah, you &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; don't want armor on with &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; around. &lt;i&gt;Definitely not.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="blindfold" />
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="1001">Oh good, now you'll be able to see how hot I am. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1073">You're like the people from the Allegory of the Cave, and it's time for you to reach enlightenment.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1074">Why would you even come to a game like this with a &lt;i&gt;blindfold&lt;/i&gt;? Were you hoping to just &lt;i&gt;smell&lt;/i&gt; how attractive your opponents are?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1072">Good, now I'll be able to look you in the eyes while I beat you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                <state img="#-threatening.png" oneShotId="627">I could kill you for that!... Just kidding. &lt;i&gt;Or am I...?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1185" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Oh right, this is the part where I tell you about something totally inane to distract you from how inane this is, huh? Let's see... Last time I broke someone's nose was when this guy challenged me, confusing his immortality for indestructibility.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="16" priority="301">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">You realize that's the kind of manipulation tactic strippers pull on people to get them to buy expensive champagne and private dances, right? </state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">What are you, a freakin' preschooler? "Aw, look at the special little ~player.ifMale(boy|girl)~! Who's gonna grow up to do great things? &lt;i&gt;You are!&lt;/i&gt;" Do you not hear how patronizing it is?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You realize that's the kind of manipulation tactic advertisers pull to get you to buy crap you don't need, right?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Like, seriously, do you have so little going on that hearing a bunch of random strip poker opponents pretend to be interested in you is the only thing that keeps you going?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I know you're not gonna trust me on this, but seriously, don't fall for such obvious manipulation tactics. People who can't tell you &lt;i&gt;why&lt;/i&gt; they like you are just playing with your emotions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="superhero" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="mask" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="180">Your secret identity is safe with me! &lt;i&gt;Not!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="766">Too bad for you, I never forget a face! I will forever know your true identity!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="773">&lt;i&gt;Real&lt;/i&gt; smart move you just made, showing your face to a super notorious villain. Can't wait to see your next &lt;i&gt;genius&lt;/i&gt; move -- sticking a fork in a toaster, maybe?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="cheats_with_clothes" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1459">I don't know if putting more clothes on is brazen enough to be respectable, or just plain cowardly. Eh, I'll just go with the negative one: &lt;i&gt;Coward!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition gender="male" role="target" layers="3-" startingLayers="4-" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="important" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make no mistake, though, no matter what order you take things off in, I'm still going to mock and jeer you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition gender="female" role="target" layers="4-" startingLayers="5-" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="major" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="important" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make no mistake, though, no matter what order you take things off in, I'm still going to mock and jeer you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="121">Did you step in something on the way here, or is that smell your feet?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="794">Be sure to keep your athlete's foot to yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="mask" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="241">&lt;i&gt;Oh god! You're hideous! Put it back on!&lt;/i&gt; Ha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="sandals" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="235">Just as well, I guess. Sandals make it almost &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; easy to smash your toes.</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="816">Bet'cha can't guess how many people I've chased -- and &lt;i&gt;caught&lt;/i&gt; -- 'cause they tripped over their own sandals!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="weapon" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="787">Not like you could've harmed me with ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="thong" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="800">Good riddance to bad lingerie.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1440">Seriously, if you're turned on by &lt;i&gt;crotch floss&lt;/i&gt;, you're crazier than I am!</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="1439">I'd rather break &lt;i&gt;my own&lt;/i&gt; leg than wear one of those!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1441">You know what's sexier than underwear that barely covers you? &lt;i&gt;Nothing. Literally not wearing anything!&lt;/i&gt; And no, that's not a complement.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="helmet" />
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="830">Nice, now I can cause you head trauma!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <state img="#-rope.png" oneShotId="259">If you're into being tied up, lemme tell you right now: You're not getting an inch of my tether! &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="260">I know I was talking up how much I want to beat you up, but if you're actually into that, I'm more interested in denying you that pleasure!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="261">Lemme tell you now: I'm &lt;i&gt;strictly&lt;/i&gt; "look but don't touch." Touching is fun, and I can't allow that, now can I?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="262">Too bad for you, I'm not the "seductive" type of villain! Why stroke a dude's nuts when you can grab him by 'em instead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" priority="1">
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="365">I'd offer to help, but... there's not much I can do.</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png" oneShotId="366">Are you into being tied up? We can probably arrange that, if we're very careful...</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png" oneShotId="367">You wouldn't happen to have an overbite fetish, would you? Haha...</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="368">I'm still not opposed to some staring, if you want...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="936">Don't hold out waiting for me to flash you or throw the game or whatever. What you see is as good as you're getting.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="35">
                <state img="#-cute.png">Am I sexy enough for you? No? &lt;i&gt;Too bad!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if there's any way I can make the other opponents less appealing for you to look at... Probably not without a level of psychological warfare inappropriate for a non-enemy...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Ugh, could you possibly &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt; any louder? &lt;i&gt;We get it, you're getting off.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; putting on your best performance, right? 'Cause I'm not feeling a thing over here! Try harder!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">If you can't manage to finish, you can just go home. I'm sure no one will be disappointed. No one &lt;i&gt;at all&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">If you wanna look at me, go ahead and look. I've got nothin' to be shy about!</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I know what you're thinking, and &lt;i&gt;yes&lt;/i&gt;, my hands &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; feel horrible against your sensitive bits. Wanna feel?</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="496">Hey, have you ever thought about masturbating with sand paper? I bet it'd be horrible! Think about it -- seriously, &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; think about it!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">You have my permission to moan my name. You're welcome.</state>
                <state img="#-arm-extended.png">Wanna borrow a hand? It'll be completely terrible, but that's exactly why I'm offering.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition role="target" timeInStage="4" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Still going? What's the matter, can't focus? Are my conversations not &lt;i&gt;sexy&lt;/i&gt; enough?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="38">
                <state img="#-arm.png">Must be a whole lot easier to focus without me taunting and threatening you, huh...?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">A-am I doing much for you? Geez, I actually care now...</state>
                <state img="#-laugh.png">At least you don't have to use &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; hands for that, right? R-right...?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You wouldn't date a girl with metal hands, would you? I mean, you wouldn't like the idea of metal hands touching down there, right? Even &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; don't like that idea, and I have to live with them...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Now that I think about it, I'm not sure how to go about making these hands softer... At least not to the point where they'd be, uh... &lt;i&gt;pleasant&lt;/i&gt; down there...</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">You're not thinking of anyone in particular, are you?... Just curious...</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I may be a genius in regards to a lot of things, but this sort of thing is... something I've not really researched...</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png">If you're thinking about my tether at all... Don't. Just don't.</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">Do you like when people speak another language to you, ~target~? Est-ce que cela fait beaucoup pour vous ? Hmm?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" priority="1">
                <state img="#-humored.png" oneShotId="271">Enjoy festering in your own fluids, chump!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="272">You're cleaning that up yourself. If you don't, I will &lt;i&gt;make you&lt;/i&gt; clean it up.</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" oneShotId="273">Nice mess, but I can make a bigger one with one arm tied behind my back &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; no stimulation! I'm talking about my bomb launcher, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="274">And now you're as irrelevant to this match as you could possibly be! How does &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; make you feel?</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Gross.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" priority="1">
                <state img="#-laugh.png" oneShotId="378">Do you feel less evil now too? Haha...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="379">Uh, do we have anything handy to clean up with?...</state>
                <state img="#-cute.png" oneShotId="380">I bet your head doesn't feel as clear as mine does! Heh heh...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="377">Uh, good job? Sorry, still pretty new to this whole "being nice" thing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="death" />
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="Death_Win1">So this makes me immortal, right? Enjoying an unending life would be the &lt;i&gt;best&lt;/i&gt; way to spite my enemies!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="279">Anyone bring any lubricant? No? &lt;i&gt;Good.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" priority="0">
                <condition filterOut="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-taunt.png" oneShotId="921">Bet you wish you could cum on my tits, huh? Keep dreaming! I'm never gonna let you do something so gross to me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-threatening.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-shrug.png">Sure hope you don't have any problems relaxing for this. I'm sure you're &lt;i&gt;totally&lt;/i&gt; not thinking about the dangerously-equipped cyborg with a penchant for violence across from you right now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great going, ~player~. You broke something. You shouldn't be seeing this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh... I think something broke. You shouldn't be seeing this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat==1" />
                <state img="custom:#-defeat">Ah!... Oh, good, it's happened again. I really wasn't sure it would.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat&gt;=2" />
                <state img="custom:#-defeat">Ah!... You did it again, ~player~! Thank you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="custom:#-defeat">Oh my god... &lt;i&gt;Oh my god&lt;/i&gt;, the evil left my body! I-I'm normal! All it took was losing at strip poker!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat==1" />
                <state img="custom:#-defeat">Ah!... Oh, good, it's happened again. I really wasn't sure it would.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat&gt;=2" />
                <state img="custom:#-defeat">Ah!... You did it again, ~player~! Thank you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="24">
                <state img="custom:#-defeat">Oh my god... &lt;i&gt;Oh my god&lt;/i&gt;, the evil left my body! I-I'm normal! All it took was losing at strip poker!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat==1" />
                <state img="#-starting.png">Oh gosh, the horny is overwhelming me again. Too bad I still haven't made my hands softer...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat&gt;=2" />
                <state img="#-starting.png">I actually kinda like losing like this. The arousal is a bit overwhelming, but it feels good... unlike these hands...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-starting.png">You have no idea how hard the evil in me was repressing my sexuality. I &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; need this right now... Gah! Geez, why'd I have to replace my arms with these chunks of metal...? Stupid cold fingers...</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">Don't worry, I'll still do the forfeit. My repressed sexuality is hitting me like a tidal wave right now... &lt;i&gt;Gah, cold fingers...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've been evil for so long, I &lt;i&gt;legitimately&lt;/i&gt; don't even know what my fetishes are...</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png" oneShotId="293">You think there's anything I can do with the--? No. No way. There's &lt;i&gt;no way&lt;/i&gt; that'd feel good...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I really should've brought a toy. Even without knowing I'd stop being evil, I should've prepared for the extremely foreseeable possibility of losing.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">Wish I had at least put rubber tips on these fingers... How the heck did I ever grasp anything with these...?</state>
                <state img="#-taunt.png">I suppose I'm not against... someone with softer hands helping me out right now...</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="1329" marker="ALittleShock">Gotta admit, the shock feature in these things is rather tempting. But without an intensity setting, there's no way to go from "knock yourself unconscious" to "pleasant tingle."</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I definitely regret not implementing a vibrate function...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="35">
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="PuttinOnTheZap">Okay... curiosity's getting the better of me. What if I did just &lt;i&gt;a little&lt;/i&gt; zap for stimulation... &lt;i&gt;Ow!&lt;/i&gt; Ow ow, okay, never doing &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; again...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" hidden="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="helper-chan" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="nickname*=Helper-sama">This line changes Helper-chan's nickname so I show her more respect after losing. I'm no longer evil, after all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Oh gosh... I'm so close... b-but I'm afraid to go too fast with these metal hands...</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">These stupid metal hands... haven't gotten any more comfortable to use...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Holy crap... I-I'm practically rubbing myself raw...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm gonna... be so sore later...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">I'll be... so glad when I'm done... and not have to stick these dangerous things anywhere down there anytime soon...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">Oh geez... there's a very real risk... of me accidentally triggering one of my weapons right now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">O-oh gosh... &lt;i&gt;Oh gosh&lt;/i&gt;... &lt;i&gt;Aaaah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-finished.png">Ah... good... I managed to do that without hurting myself with these arms.</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">I... am &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; glad I did that without injuring myself...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="23">
                <condition role="opp" character="critical_darling" sayingMarker="NeroForteStory" />
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="TheGoodInNero">Y'know... I actually feel bad for Nero, now that I can see the good he tried to do... I think... I think he was just trying to prove that &lt;i&gt;everyone&lt;/i&gt; is capable of redeeming themselves...</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="ScaredOfNero">I wouldn't have admitted it before, but Nero scared me. I would've ended up just like Crosshair if I couldn't manage to catch him by surprise -- would've smashed my arms and beat me to death with his bare fists.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="22">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NewArms" />
                <state img="#-rope.png">The grapple feature &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; pretty useful... and I should probably keep a weapon or two just in case... Eh, maybe it'd be easier just to tweak these than it'd be to start from scratch...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="32">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="UnevilTheory" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do you think my evil side will return? If it does, maybe I can learn to control it -- y'know, like the Hulk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="34">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="UnfoundedFears" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="TheGoodYouMiss">Lemme just prove my earlier point: When's the last time you heard about some crime going down? Pretty recently, I bet. When's the last time you heard about someone holding the door for a stranger? Or helping someone reach an item on the top shelf? The "Penny Challenge?" &lt;i&gt;Exactly.&lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-arm.png" oneShotId="9">Hey, um... For what it's worth, I'm sorry about... literally everything I've said here...</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" oneShotId="682">I wonder if any of my friends still like me...? I probably made them all hate me... Wait, they were all villains, what do I care what they think of me?...</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png">I'm glad Golden Glory pushed so hard for prison reform. Even after all I've done, I should be out on good behavior in no time.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png">It's gonna be so hard to get a job. It's hard enough for &lt;i&gt;small-time&lt;/i&gt; criminals to get them, let alone &lt;i&gt;super villains&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">To think I laughed at Raven's desire to help reform villains... It'd be pretty embarrassing to see him again after this...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if we can get the evil out of Grizelda too...? Ah, but it's not gonna be easy to convince her to try...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">On the bright side, I may not be evil anymore, but I'm still a genius. I could probably still go pretty far...</state>
                <state img="#-rope.png" oneShotId="681" marker="NewArms">When I get home, I'll have to build myself a much, &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; less dangerous pair of arms... I'll keep the same color scheme, though. It's nice...</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png">I still can't believe I got myself off with these...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="321">I really meant it when I said I'm a people person, by the way. But now I don't have a love for messing with people in the way of that.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="328" marker="EvilSinceBirth">So, um... Yeah, I've been evil since birth, and I committed myself so hard to villainy that I never gave myself time for boyfriends... or girlfriends, for that matter. I'm not even sure if I'm into girls... or boys either... I'll have to do some soul-searching later...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="484">Sorry if I start repeating myself a lot. BlueKoin didn't expect people to see much of this stage, so he didn't write a whole lot of not-evil dialogue for me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="515" marker="UnevilTheory">So... Any theories as to why I suddenly un-eviled? Currently, my best guess is that losing at a game I was cheating at caused my evil to hit critical mass and basically go supernova.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Honestly? I'm as surprised as I am disappointed my skin and hair were both that way 'cause of the evil. It was a pretty good look.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Y'know, I could probably give pretty decent electrode massages with these hands... Once I work in an intensity-setting function...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="1211" marker="UnfoundedFears">Here's a positive thought: Most of our fears are unfounded. When we see bad things happening on the news, we only accept them as "the way things are" to validate our fears, when in reality, everything we hear about is only a &lt;i&gt;fraction&lt;/i&gt; of what's actually happening in the world.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1276" marker="TrulyDontLetsStart">Y'know, I think John Linnell got it right when he sang "No one in the world ever gets what they want and that is beautiful." There's some ironic comfort that comes from the idea that it's impossible to live a completely content life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="25" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" filter="dc_comics" role="opp" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="NotScaredOfSuperman" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Honestly, if Batman were real, I don't think I could've beaten him when I was evil -- yeah, that's right. I wasn't scared of the most OP super hero ever but I'm scared of the guy known for having &lt;i&gt;no&lt;/i&gt; powers. No powers means no Kryptonite!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="26" priority="0">
                <condition count="0" filter="dc_comics" role="opp" />
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="NotScaredOfSuperman" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Honestly, if Batman were real, I don't think I could've beaten him when I was evil. &lt;i&gt;Every&lt;/i&gt; villain thinks they can outsmart him and never do. I don't think I'm special.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" oneShotId="27" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="OrderOfBozos" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do you think any super heroes I encounter from here on will believe I'm no longer evil?... They probably won't -- especially the Order of Heroes. They're, uh... not exactly keen on redemption.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="+Victory">Better luck next time, losers!</state>
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="+Victory">Let that be a lesson. No matter how many opponents I face at once, I'll still come out on top!</state>
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="+Victory">Like I already said, you've gotta try &lt;i&gt;a lot&lt;/i&gt; harder than that to beat me. Why don't we try this again when you can gather up seven more people to try to beat me with! &lt;i&gt;Ha!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="+Victory">This would be the part where I say "Now screw off," but you already &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt;, so... I'll just see myself out.</state>
                <state img="#-arm.png" marker="+Victory">Another bunch of chumps thoroughly defeated by yours truly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Victory&gt;=2" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="+Victory">Try as many times as you want, you're not gonna beat me!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="+Victory">I'm happy to keep thrashing ya as many times as you want! Come lose to me again sometime.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="+Victory">Let this be a lesson: Don't challenge me at &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;! I'll always wipe the floor with you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-7">
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="+Victory">A suboptimal victory, but a victor nonetheless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="+Victory">I won the game, but you saw my tits, so really &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; the winners. Yeah, that's right, I'll let you have that victory.</state>
                <state img="#-disgust.png" marker="+Victory">Would've preferred to win &lt;i&gt;before&lt;/i&gt; you saw anything from me -- not out of embarrassment, but for the sake of denying you something.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="PityMode" />
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="PlayerNoPityWin">
                    <text>Hey, congrats, ~player~! You beat me, and I didn't even have to go easy on you!</text>
                    <markers>
                        <marker name="Defeat" op="+" value="1" />
                    </markers>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Defeat==2" />
                <state img="#-humored.png" marker="+Defeat">Wow, you actually beat me twice in a row? Are you sure &lt;i&gt;you're&lt;/i&gt; not the cheater?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="+Defeat">So you beat me twice in a row, huh? I don't have anything to give you, so, uh... Take a picture, or something?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="+Defeat">So I lost twice in a row? Should that even be possible?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-laugh.png" marker="+Defeat">Wow, who would've thought that losing a game of strip poker would be so life changing? I'm going home literally a changed woman!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="PityMode" />
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-shrug.png" marker="+Defeat">Hey, um, hate to spoil your victory, ~player~, but there's still some evil in me, and she's telling me to tell you that you beat me on "pity mode." You're gonna have to try again if you want proper bragging rights.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" collectible="collectible_x">Huh. Not sure what this thing is. Dunno how it got there...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
