<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.9 at 8:41:16 AM on March 31, 2024. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.9</version>
    <first>Fairy</first>
    <last>Leviathan</last>
    <label>Leviathan</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>small</size>
    <timer>34</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">good</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="crotch plate" generic="armor" position="lower" type="major" />
        <clothing name="cuirass" generic="armor" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="bodysuit" generic="bodysuit" position="both" type="important" />
        <clothing name="helmet" generic="helmet" position="head" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="gloves" generic="gloves" position="arms" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="phase_strip">
            <sprite id="stripping" src="#-stripping.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <sprite id="teleport" delay="0.5" src="#-teleport.png" x="0" y="0" scalex="1" scaley="1" />
            <directive type="animation" id="stripping" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="#-stripping.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.5" src="#-stripped.png" />
                <keyframe time="1" src="#-flourish.png" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="teleport" delay="0.5" ease="linear" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="0" y="0" scalex="1" />
                <keyframe time="0.06999999" x="0" y="0" scalex="1.3" />
                <keyframe time="0.12" x="0" y="0" scalex="0.05" />
                <keyframe time="0.4" y="-1200" scalex="0" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="teleport" delay="0.5" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="#-teleport.png" scaley="1" />
                <keyframe time="0.06999999" scaley="0.95" />
                <keyframe time="0.12" scaley="1" />
                <keyframe time="0.4" scaley="0" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
    </poses>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh? What's this? Are we playing a game?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What do we have here? A game? Can I play?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What's going on here? Something fun?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-playful.png">Yes! Let's play! Let's play! I was just feeling bored!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">"Strip Poker," huh? I'll play by your silly rules, so long as you don't bore me!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">This should be fun! Come on! Let's start already!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmm... how about ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Yes, I'll take ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~. That's what I need.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~ now. Come on! Come on!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh, I'll keep you in suspense. It's more fun that way!</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Do your best. I don't know if it will matter, but give it a try anyway. For fun!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Let's go! Let's go! Let's see who lost this time!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">... You. I think it's you who's going to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">No need to be nervous. Just take a deep breath and prepare to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu! Show me your cards! I want to know who lost!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... which one is the loser? I wonder...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Don't forget to put a little effort into it when you lose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Let's have you struggle some more.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I'm glad you've kept it interesting, but just don't forget you're going to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Don't overthink your next move. It's not going to matter anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Please, make me put you back in your place. It's more fun that way!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">You're out of your depth!</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Oh, look! Time for me to be entertained again!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Do you feel that chill? You will...</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">You're in way over your head!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nfufu. Exciting little game...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm? What's the hold-up? Wouldn't you rather lose now than later?</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Even the strong need just a little bit of luck.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Are you ready to take the plunge?</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Don't stop now! Let's keep cruising along!</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">How do humans come up with these silly little games?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Winning isn't everything, but it is more fun that way.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Maybe you could beat me! Just maybe! Winning is more fun when it's difficult!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Underestimating you would be foolish. I know better than that by now.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What's the fun in worrying? It's fun to watch you do it! That's the fun!</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Show me a good time...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Just need to stay cool...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu! Let's see if you can best me again!</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Go ahead and surprise me. Just don't mess it up...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">No more overwhelming victory. At least humiliating you is worth the effort.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">I like this game! All these dumb rules keep it exciting!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Hmph... coming up dry...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Would have been a lot better if I got what I wanted...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This might be exciting...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Well this seems more than a little fishy...</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Tch. It's so dusty up here...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">I do better in the water...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I guess I am a little out of my element up here.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Ugh, what's with the lousy luck?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-defiant.png">This isn't helping with my killer comeback!</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Once again, I'm struggling as things start heating up...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Oh, this isn't going as perfectly as I imagined....</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">You're really making me work for it, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-defiant.png">It doesn't matter! There's still no escape from your defeat!</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Tch. How frustrating...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Must be all this dry air throwing me off...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">At least this is better than just being bored...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="nephenee_resp0_1">Nfufu. Thank you. A warrior must always be at the ready, don't you agree?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="nephenee_resp1_1">I am a reploid, ~nephenee~. A &lt;i&gt;reploid&lt;/i&gt;. A synthetic being made to aid and protect humanity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="nephenee_resp2_1">I'm well accustomed to fighting with it on; moreover, it helps me maneuver in the water. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="nephenee_resp3_1">I'm a hero, ~nephenee~, aren't I allowed to be a little conceited now and then? And is it really conceit when I'm actually so great?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="nephenee_resp4_1">The ocean is my home. I try not to leave too often, but sometimes the fight or the fun or the two at once are surface-side.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-ready.png" marker="nephenee_resp5_1">You've proven more competent than I first thought, even for a bumpkin.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-playful.png">Oh? It's my turn? Okay! Here we go!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Looks like it's my turn! This part should be fun too!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Too bad! Looks like I can't win them all, huh? Nfufu!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-playful.png">Not going down without a fight, huh? I can appreciate that!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh, you got me again. Not bad. Maybe this will stay interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Me again? Okay then, here I go!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Got me again. I bet you think you deserve a reward. Let's just stick with the usual, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu. It's my turn again! Seems I shouldn't underestimate your determination.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Maybe you just got lucky again, but a win is a win. I'll give you what you want.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nobody can completely control their luck, so savor whatever victories you can get.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">See? This is why I'm bothering to stick around. I want to see just how close you get to taking me out!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nfufu... I'm impressed, but not surprised. Fine, here's another reward for your efforts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nfufu! Well done! I hope you don't give up just because you're getting something you've wanted so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">I had a feeling it would come to this. Very well, you have the reward you so deeply desire: my respect. Oh, and a closer look at my body.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">What is it that drives you? Is it that you just don't want to lose? Or is there something you desperately are trying to see before you do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-ready.png">You've kept things fun and exciting for me this whole time. Losing like this... I don't think I mind.</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">This has been more fun than I imagined. Looks like I'll have the perfect chance to show my gratitude.</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Fine. You've come this far. I'm more than happy to reward you for keeping me entertained.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">That's just how it goes. I didn't think I'd get out of this without a scratch.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm? It's me? Okay! I can show myself off a little bit.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">So much for a total victory. Oh well. It'll be more fun if I get to strip a little too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh, this silly little game. Okay, here I go again.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Losing the first time was kind of fun. I was actually hoping I might get another chance to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu. I'll go again. I'd be glad to, even. It certainly keeps things interesting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're making this harder than I thought you would. Take that as a compliment.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Am I going to have to start taking this more seriously? I don't want you to think I'm push-over.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're determined to keep this interesting, huh? I can appreciate that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-wondering.png">These human games are trickier than they seem on the surface...</state>
                <state img="#-defiant.png">H-how frustrating! You're just getting lucky!</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Now this is a league too far. What am I doing wrong?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... maybe a little peek at paradise will take a little of the fight out of you...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Whether it's luck or sheer determination, I guess I have to admit you've got me fighting against the current. Fine, here's a reward...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Silly little game. This is the entire point, right? Will your will to fight be depleted if I do this for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Placing me right on the edge of victory and defeat? Exciting...</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Enjoy your luck while it lasts. You haven't seen the last of me yet!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I didn't imagine I'd have this much trouble. This game is so stimulating. I think I love it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Very well, I'll go ahead and strip. Just don't get too used to it, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">There's a first time for everything. Even I'm not perfectly lucky.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... stripping could be fun. I don't think I mind losing this round so much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">... Fine, I'll take another turn. Honestly, I think it would be fun if you lost a little more.</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Of course. You didn't get enough of me the first time. Okay, watch carefully this time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh, poor me. I guess it will be fun to strip again, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Don't get cocky, alright? Your luck could just as easily start sinking...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Fine, fine. I'll keep playing along. Just don't count on this continuing.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I just can't seem to find an edge. Maybe I should do something about that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-defiant.png">I'm not seriously getting beat? A-at this ridiculous game?</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">That's nothing but luck! It's just too dusty up here for me to fully concentrate! That's all it is!</state>
                <state img="#-envious.png">This is dumb. Why aren't I winning?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">But I'm not supposed to be losing! I'm superior! Me!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">So frustrating! So frustrating! So frustrating! So frustrating!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">What's with all this rotten luck? Why can't I destroy you?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" set-intelligence="best">T-this isn't over! Don't think you've beaten me!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" set-intelligence="best">It's nothing but luck! This isn't fair! I should come out on top!</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" set-intelligence="best">I'm not going out like this! Not for a second! This is the last time I'm going to lose!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s2_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp2_2">The best protection for something as fragile as you is for someone like me to stand between you and danger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" stage="4-7" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s2_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp2_2">That is what it's designed for, but it doesn't explain why you're so weirdly attached to it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s0_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp0_2">I always have access to the Frost Javelin if I need it, but I can't imagine I will. If I thought this place was dangerous, I wouldn't be playing this little game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s1_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp1_2">Hmm. Perhaps this is just a concept that is above your understanding.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s3_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp3_2">I wouldn't really know. I don't really take criticism from my lessers. I don't get a lot of gratitude either. I destroy the enemy and move along.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s4_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp4_2">Nfufu. Maybe being out of my element for so long has put me a little on edge. I mean, what else could it be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s5_2" />
                <state img="custom:phase_strip" marker="nephenee_resp5_2">Nfufu. I just don't know what to make of you. You give me such a hard time but you don't even understand what I am.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="31">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">I don't get a lot of chances to interact with humans like this. Most of them are afraid of reploids.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">I am a little surprised a human would want to play a game like this with a reploid. Normally you're too terrified.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Never been invited to play a human game before. Usually you're so wary of reploids.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">I don't normally let anyone see my like this. Only my brothers and Master X have had the privilege.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Yes, the helmet does come off. Consider yourselves lucky, as only the other guardians have ever seen me like this.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Lucky you. You get to see my full, unimpeded beauty. Such a rare sight that only a select few have seen it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">I hope this doesn't take too long for me to win. I don't like being out of the water for too long.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">It is a little hard for me to relax here on the surface. It's much better to be underwater where I can just float around...</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Too bad we can't play this underwater, but this seems fun enough to stay on the surface for. Just not too long.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">As a reploid designed to serve humanity, I'm as human as possible so that I might better understand them...</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Surprised by how human I am? Not all reploids are, but it is critical to my mission that I'm able to understand humans...</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">So why would a reploid be so similar to humans? It's simple, really: it helps me better understand and thus better serve them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">How much do you even know about reploids? Are you wondering "what is even going on under there?" Perv.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Are you excited to see all the ways a reploid is different from a human? All the ways we're better?</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">While you're ogling my body, please don't forget that I'm a reploid. It's just not fair to other humans to compare me to them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">So, here's the answer to your big question: yes, I have a vagina. Pretty, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Humans have called reploids "soulless war-machines." Maybe that's right, but why would a "soulless war-machine" have a pretty little pussy like this?</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Some reploids have tails. Some reploids have wings. Some have horns. Me? I've got tight little cunt.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" stage="0-3" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png" marker="nephenee_resp2_3">This has nothing to do with being grown, ~nephenee~. It's just a matter of who's best for the job.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" stage="4-6" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="nephenee_resp2_3">Doesn't seem to be keeping you safe from being humiliated!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" stage="7" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="nephenee_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-mocking.png" marker="nephenee_resp2_3">Did you happen to see how I got my helmet off without crying?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="nephenee_resp0_3">Of course I don't. I don't lug it around with me when I don't need it. If and when I do, it will come to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-playful.png" marker="nephenee_resp1_3">Nfufu. There's no need to be jealous! Not yet, at least!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="nephenee_resp3_3">Sure, but there I am getting my socialization in. Don't ruin it by being all gloomy. Say more of your funny country-isms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="nephenee_resp4_2">N-no! I'm &lt;i&gt;flawless&lt;/i&gt;, okay? &lt;i&gt;Flawless!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="nephenee" sayingMarker="Leviathan_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png" marker="nephenee_resp5_3">Amazing. That's even worse than I was expecting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Of course, there's no reason for a human to be afraid of me. I've pledged to protect humanity. Still, I will absolutely stomp you at this game.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">I'm glad there are humans who aren't so afraid of reploids they won't play with us! Alright, now I'm going to beat you terribly at this game of yours!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">As a reploid pledged to guard humanity, I'm no threat to you, so just relax. Oh, but I will completely destroy you at this little game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-yawn.png">Just make sure you don't bore me or I'll just go straight back to the ocean.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do humans even have underwater games? They couldn't be very long games since you can't hold your breath all that long.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I guess the cards would all float away if we were underwater. Well, all the best underwater games involve racing anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So, do I seem more human this way? Try and remember that I'm a reploid.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I could almost pass for a human girl like this, couldn't I? Even if you fall in love with me, make sure to remember I'm a reploid!</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">So, what do you think? Didn't think a reploid could be so human and captivating? I bet that's what you're thinking!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Of course, this game wouldn't be at all interesting to me if I wasn't interested in your bodies either...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">"Perfect" isn't a word I usually use to describe myself, but you can if you want!</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Well, comparison is inevitable. Maybe it wouldn't hurt if we call got a close look at all the differences...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Still, a reploid is obviously different from a human in a few ways. And by "different" I mean "better."</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">I'm even receptive to sexual stimuli. I think of it as a gift to have a body with the capacity for such pleasure...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Even if you understand why I'm so close to being human, I'm sure the next question is "why is she so beautiful?" </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I know my body may stimulate your biological desire to procreate, but all attempts to do so with me would prove futile. No matter how many times you try it...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">See? It even gets moist when I'm aroused. ..</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">While I'm sure it's very much like a human's, I've never actually gotten a human's opinion on it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Have fun, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu! Time to put on a show for us!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh, ~target~, how unfortunate. I just don't see you being able to beat me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you're not holding back just because I'm a woman.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">There's no pressure, ~target~. Not like I haven't seen what a human man looks like naked before.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Oooh, ~target~'s turn? He's pretty cute!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Poor ~target~. There's your drop of pity, so go ahead and strip!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let's see how you handle this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Poor, poor, ~target~. Then again, I have no pity left for you.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu! I want ~target~ to get his comeuppance...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You still have so much to offer, ~target~. So much you owe...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're not getting away that easily...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Yes. Good. Someone needs to pay.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I might not be the winner, but at least I can still see ~target~ get what's coming to him.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Not so tough anymore, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Serves him right...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">That's what you get for getting cocky...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Mmph... I'm reminded of my failure...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">I could use a little entertainment...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Let's have it, ~target~. Don't disappoint me...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Try as you might, a human is just no match for a reploid. That's just how it is.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">You're going to have to to better than that if you want to win. Maybe you'd rather lose and sate your lust? Typical.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Are you even trying? You'd better put more effort into getting your clothes off.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">You might not go down easy, but you &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; go down, human.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Boohoo, ~target~. &lt;i&gt;Strip&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Go ahead, ~target~. Let's see what you're made of.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">You are pretty for a human. Too bad about your poor luck!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Human women have certain charms to them. I don't think they'll be replaced by reploids... yet.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmm... it remains to be seen if you're really a worthy opponent.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Don't worry, ~target~. I know what a naked human woman looks like.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu! ~Target~ lost! That's just too bad for her! Nfufu!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I could pretend to pity you, but I know your time is precious.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let's see what a human woman is capable of...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm the last one here you should expect to take it easy on you.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I'm not going to miss out on my chance to humiliate you. It's far too fun...</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Are you getting distracted by your urges? Or maybe you're just giving into them?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Remember not to bore me...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">So sorry, ~target~. Seems a human woman just pales in comparison to a reploid.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Complain if you want, but the result is the same.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Serves her right...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">Not so easy for humans now, is it?</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Maybe it does all boil down to luck...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Well... if you're willing to put on a show...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Why by a good sport when being a sore loser is so much more cathartic?</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Not so hot now, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I'm not leaving until someone pays for my humiliation. ~Target~ is certainly on the list of acceptable targets.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, the faces you'll make when you finally lose it all...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm watching someone else fail and ~target~ is very, very deserving of it.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I feel for you ~target~, I really do; however, in a larger sense I want you to pay for contributing to my humiliation.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Where has all your good fortune run off to now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-bored.png">So that's it? Nothing happens? Boooring...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm sorry. Did I forget to specifically request not to be bored?</state>
                <state img="#-yawn.png">You're just delaying the inevitable...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Isn't this game supposed to be exciting? What is exciting about this?</state>
                <state img="#-yawn.png">Hm, small effort for a small result...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I fail to see how ~clothing.ifPlural(these things|this thing)~ is an impediment to your masturbating.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is that all you have to show us? Really?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Are you not driven mad with lust yet? Do you really not want to lose so badly?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">... Fine, fine, just get it over with.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Clearly we'll just have you lose again!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's no fun unless you're willing to suffer just a little bit. And then a little bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't think for a moment that you're about to get away with that pitiful display.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">... I guess it's still worth it to try and wring more out of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-cross.png">Squander your opportunity to impress me. See if I care.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You must have more to offer. What will it take to pry it out of you?</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">You're not cool enough to get away with being this lame.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Still... I have to respect someone who doesn't give up easily...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bored.png">That's boring. You're boring me.</state>
                <state img="#-yawn.png">If you're trying to discourage me from defeating you... it's working.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">This is not what I am enduring this dry, dusty place to see...</state>
                <state img="#-yawn.png">You'll never win if you don't take risks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">Why don't you just leave that on? Get to the good stuff already...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is that all you have to show us? Really?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">You wouldn't rather, I don't know, do something interesting right about now?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Right, right take your time. Just nevermind that it's our time too.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Why don't we continue? I think ~target~ deserves to lose again as quickly as possible.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You will have another chance to be properly humiliated.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It doesn't matter in the end. Don't think for a second I'm actually just going to let you defeat me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It really is fine. I'll just keep the momentum going...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-cross.png">Showing off your lucky you are is not as impressive as you think.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">There's no escaping your inevitable fall...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">Can we move on any faster from this?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sorry, ~target~, but remember that I'm a reploid. I'm not going get all sentimental about every little trinket.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Go ahead. Get your ~clothing~ off. I'll wait...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I guess this is better than nothing.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Even if you take your time stripping, I won't take my time defeating you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You'd be worthier of effort if you had a bit more daring in you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Meh. Fine. Just know I'm not impressed.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">This is just the start! Don't forget!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Little by little, the tide comes in...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Relish your safety while you can...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">How many more of those have you got in you? Let's find out!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Don't be shy, ~target~. We're going to see everything anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You just haven't realized yet that you're about to get swept away!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Feel a chill? That's your last chance at victory dying out in the cold!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, yes. Seeing more of you would be ideal...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Don't you want to show off? Why let the chance be swept away?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Why not dive in head-first? The cold shock might be invigorating...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Whether you feel shame or pride in your nudity, you'll be in it anyway. Consider just speeding up the process.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Why be modest? Why not take this chance to really let loose?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I understand going piece by piece... but I still think you could make it more interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">You can go bit by bit, but you'll only be agonizing yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Hmm... I still think you could make this interesting. You just might be worthy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Still waiting for you to get to the good part...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">So you've got a hard shell to crack, but apply enough pressure...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh, when will you share your pretty little secrets with us?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Still just a little too comfortable...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" sayingMarker="keyblade_reveal" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm, neat trick... for a human.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Oh? Something to bash things with? Seems a human ought to use something that puts more distance between you and danger.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu. That's cute. Weapons designed for humans are so amusing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Have I gotten into your head yet? Do you feel yourself getting psyched out?</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">The tide is creeping up on you, ~target~. How's your swimming?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Maybe this is the beginning of the end for you. </state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">All it takes is one little slip and suddenly you can't win again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">If you weren't ready to share, then you wouldn't be playing with us. Could you just be teasing?</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Are you beginning to feel the excitement? Isn't it getting you going?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Isn't it frustrating to have so much stuff in the way of being free? Wouldn't you rather just skip to the end?</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Don't you hear the siren call of desire? Singing... singing...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oooh, now it's getting interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Getting ready for high waters?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Someone wants to rise to the challenge...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Oh? Way to keep it exciting, ~target~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Hmm, come on in. The water's fine...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Such a strange game, but you can't argue with the results.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Of course I am curious to see how you're built...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">So your luck is terrible? At least you've got an attractive body for us to see...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-flirting.png">This is nice, but I'm going to need to extract even more from you...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">... No, I still want more.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Now we can really begin to have some fun...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">But there's still so much more for you to show us. Time to lose again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Oooh... is that a bit of thaw I'm feeling?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well done, but I hope you're not anticipating with getting away with just that...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Nfufu. Embarrassed yet? I still think you need some more teasing...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Now&lt;/i&gt; we're having fun!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh, you are certainly worthy of defeat...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">After you've got your ~clothing~ off, maybe you'd like to take a nice, refreshing swim!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, isn't this a treat? I'm not around many human women and female reploids are incredibly uncommon nowadays.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">See, this is why I wanted to play with you! I knew it wouldn't stay dull!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, well, won't we make a fine pair of specimens...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Finally. I'm so very curious as to how you're put together.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Naturally I'm curious. Clearly you're made of different stuff than me.</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">There comparison between is is going to be quite fascinating considering there's no one and nothing quite like me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Now how am I going to get you into the water...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... I never gave much though to what my preferences are when it comes to bodies...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">This is a whole different sort of excitement...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is good... but I'm still in the mood for something a bit more &lt;i&gt;personal&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Are you sure you weren't designed to be lovely?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're quite the catch, but there's nothing in the ocean that can compete with me!</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Nfufu. Let's play a little more...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Let's not have you stop there. I still think there are some far more interesting sights you can show us.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="1">Oh? Does this mean you want me to take you seriously?</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="2">Don't hold back! You're not going to need ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~ when I get you into the water!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="3">This is really the least you could do if you wanted me to view you as a sexual prospect.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="4">Nfufu! Making you take off your clothes is fun! Now let's see your embarrassed face!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="10">If you're taking ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off anyway, then maybe we should take this into the water...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="11">Not too fast now. You need to make this all worth my while...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="9">If you think it'll be good enough to impress &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, then go right ahead...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="12">Go ahead and submit yourself to my judgment. I can only promise to be fair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="32">Nfufu. Now I won't be able to stop until I see your defeated face...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="33">Hmm... someone is looking utterly defenseless...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="34">You're even less capable than I expected, but there are other factors that make you entertaining.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="35">Nfufu. It's decided. It will be worthwhile to continue putting you through your paces.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="52">Seeing a man like this... does awaken something...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="53">I'd love to get a feel, if you can tolerate an icy touch...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="54">Hmm, now I'm the one feeling a chill...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="55">Nfufu. Maybe I can find a use for you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="63">Biological reproduction. So primitive, but so fascinating.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="60">Sexual organs are superfluous on reploids. We have far more elegant and efficient methods of reproduction.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="61">Ostensibly, this is some measure of your viability as a mate, right?</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="62">Poor ~target~. Made to expose his most vulnerable part and subject himself to base humiliation. What fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="72">Normally, I don't much care for this sort of thing, but right now...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="73">Yes! Show us! Show us! Don't you dare be a disappointment!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="74">Surely you're not nervous? Not after how far we've come?</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="75">Finally! A way to get your true and honest opinion about how you're feeling!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="80">Hm. Seems genetics were unkind to you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="81">So you're a poor specimen in the end? I could have guessed.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="82">No, no, I'm actually not disappointed. To be disappointed would have required me actually expecting something of substance in the first place.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="83">Isn't it kind of small? So you're not just a loser, you're a pathetic loser?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="625">Oh, well, that's good to know. If I was going to engage in intercourse, I'd rather it be with somebody worthwhile.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="626">Too bad, ~target~, but bigger is better. More strength. More stamina. More speed. Just more everything. You are... less! Nfufu!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="627">It takes confidence to play this game with such a pathetic showing, but I think it's more likely that you're just an idiot!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="628">See, if you had been designed for intercourse, you would have been given tools that would actually allow you to properly execute that function. Not whatever that is.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="92">Ooh. Not bad. I suppose it wouldn't be a waste of time to test your competence as a lover.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="93">Nfufu. There is something enticing about having a man's penis lain bare in front of you...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="94">Well, it certainly &lt;i&gt;looks&lt;/i&gt; adequate. I wonder if that can be said for its other qualities.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="95">Hmm, your humiliation is lacking, but this part of you is... satisfactory.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="100">Curiosity just leading into more curiosity...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="101">So, is that where you're feeling all of &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; yearning?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="102">I did not expect to feel so... interested...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="103">Seems you are worthy of taking down...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="525">Whatever designer crafted you seems to have intended you for breeding...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="526">A penis that size is quite perverse, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="527">It would be my preference to work with something that can really make a splash...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="528">No wonder you were willing to play. You wanted to show off your toy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="121">You're equipped with the right stuff...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="122">But does he have the strength and stamina to match...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="123">You... might be more than worthy...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="120">It might be difficult, but that could make it all the more pleasurable...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="324">This is something I'd been curious about...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="325">I had been thinking about those this whole time...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="326">See, I've been meaning to say something about those...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="131">The human fascination with breasts is well documented. Their preferences always seem to skew towards the... barbaric.</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="129">I do not personally understand the human interest in this part of the anatomy. The attachment of ego to it is ridiculous... a-and pointless!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="130">There's no point in comparing this part of a human with a reploid. Yours serve a biological function while mine are purely aesthetic. Understand? Good...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="128">I know this is very fascinating for humans, but for me it's... it is just below my interests... t-that is all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-defiant.png" oneShotId="204">~Target~! Let us agree that there is no hierarchy when it comes to breast size! It is a purely random and inconsequential! It doesn't &lt;i&gt;mean&lt;/i&gt; anything!</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="205">Y-you don't &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off, ~target~. It should not prove a hindrance to masturbation. You could lose with it on...</state>
                <state img="#-defiant.png" oneShotId="206">Just remember: reploids and humans are still fundamentally different. Th-the standard of quality  between the two is objectively different!</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png" oneShotId="207">Right, right. This was also inevitable. Let's remember that ~target~ is the one who lost and is therefore the object of ridicule. Not anyone else. Just her.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="338">The fact that we're the same is just proof that small is just the better design! Don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="339">It seems we share some design philosophy. This type of body is much better for us, don't you agree?</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="337">Your body is the only type that makes sense for us! It's the best, wouldn't you agree?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="192">Isn't this the form best suited for a woman? Sleek and refined? No unnecessary burdens?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="193">Good to know there are humans with such splendid design.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="194">Beautiful. Not a fault to be found. You have a body everyone can enjoy.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="195">Oh, dear ~target~, never change. It would be a crime to mess with perfection.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="184">Well, I must say you are a shining example of human beauty--- no, of beauty full stop!</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="185">As if your body were designed by a committee determined to reach nothing less than perfection!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="186">I hope you are aware just how perfect you are. It is remarkable that a human subject to so many random variables in their design could be so beautifully proportioned.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="187">For you, ~target~, I had a notion you were a beautiful piece of work from the very beginning! Anyone could tell just from looking!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="347">Why were you made with a chest like that? What possible function could it serve?</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png" oneShotId="348">Whenever they made you they decided to give you such an indecent form. I assume you were designed by a committee of perverts.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="349">I just don't understand why you would be designed with a chest like that. I can only assume you were intended to serve some sexual purpose...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="176">Yes, fine, very nice. Let's not get ourselves all worked up about them.</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png" oneShotId="177">I'm sure you believe you're more than adequate. I'm not saying you're not, just that I'm sure you know that you are...</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png" oneShotId="178">This is fairly standard for a human, right? No need to go overboard with the praise...</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png" oneShotId="179">Yes, yes, very attractive. Highly desirable. We can move right along.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="252">M-my body's form serves a purpose. Unnecessary ballast would slow me down in the water...</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png" oneShotId="253">N-nothing wrong with a body like yours. I just fail to see the rational behind excess...</state>
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="254">Yours aren't even that big, but they're still... bigger...</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png" oneShotId="255">I don't get what the huge deal is. It's not like they're that much bigger...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="353">... Why were they made so big? Why did I come out so... not big?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="354">I-It's obvious some boob-loving human designed your body! Y-you're just the product of some pervert with no ethics and b-bad taste!</state>
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="355">M-maybe if I wasn't designed to be so much like the other guardians, then I could have been more... &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="240">... If I had a chest like that... I'd float...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="241">S-so unnecessary... s-s-so frustrating...</state>
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="242">I-I'm supposed to be superior, so why are hers...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="243">W-whatever! You're still a loser you... you &lt;i&gt;floatation device!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="292">N-not better, just different. Definitely not better...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="293">Y-yeah?! W-well, get over yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-envious.png" oneShotId="294">Energy crystals have zero fat content, unlike whatever it is you've been eating...</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" oneShotId="295">So I wasn't made to feed babies! Big deal! Anyone with a bottle and formula can get that done just fine!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="390">Showing someone this part of you is very, very intimate. You must be so embarrassed right now.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="391">It will be hard to deny you're not just the slightest bit excited by all this when we can all see the state of your arousal...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="392">Don't forget to show us with a bit of fanfare. After all, this is your most private place we're about to see.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="393">If you're think this is embarrassing, just wait and see...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="72">Don't worry, ~target~. My interest has somewhat evolved from just humiliating you.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="73">Now this promises to be exciting! Let's see! Let's see!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="74">We're not making the most of our time until everyone has revealed their secrets...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="75">Are you nervous, ~target~? Could it be because you're already wet? You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; to show us!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="406">Hmm... it is a bit hard to embarrass you when you end up being so lovely.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="407">It's almost a shame you're the only one who will be handling yourself to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="408">Tell us. Do you feel a yearning down there? An itch to reach down and... release yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="405">As fun as this is, it does open the mind to even more fun ideas...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="413">You should go around like this more often...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="414">Fair warning for later: my hands are very cold.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="415">Nfufu. You look healthy enough for more rigorous activities than this...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="416">You'll get used to it... or you won't. You'd be cute whether you were denying your enjoyment or reveling in it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="390">Showing someone this part of you is very, very intimate. You must be so embarrassed right now.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="391">It will be hard to deny you're not just the slightest bit excited by all this when we can all see the state of your arousal...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="392">Don't forget to show us with a bit of fanfare. After all, this is your most private place we're about to see.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="393">If you're think this is embarrassing, just wait and see...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="72">Don't worry, ~target~. My interest has somewhat evolved from just humiliating you.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="73">Now this promises to be exciting! Let's see! Let's see!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="74">We're not making the most of our time until everyone has revealed their secrets...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png" oneShotId="75">Are you nervous, ~target~? Could it be because you're already wet? You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; to show us!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="445">Hm. I was really hoping for something big. At least something not small.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="446">So you're a poor specimen in the end? I could have guessed.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="447">No, no, I'm actually not disappointed. To be disappointed would have required me actually expecting something of substance in the first place.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="448">Isn't it kind of small? So you're not just a loser, you're a pathetic loser?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="613">Oh, well, that's good to know. If I was going to engage in intercourse, I'd rather it be with somebody worthwhile.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="614">Too bad, ~target~, but bigger is better. More strength. More stamina. More speed. Just more everything. You are... less! Nfufu!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="615">It takes confidence to play this game with such a pathetic showing, but I think it's more likely that you're just an idiot!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="616">See, if you had been designed for intercourse, you would have been given a tool suited for the task. Think about it. Why have a sardine when there's tuna?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="457">Ooh. Not bad. I suppose it wouldn't be a waste of time to test your competence as a lover.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="458">Nfufu. There is something enticing about having a penis lain bare in front of you...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="459">Well, it certainly &lt;i&gt;looks&lt;/i&gt; adequate. I wonder if that can be said for its other qualities.</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="460">Hmm, your humiliation is lacking, but this part of you is... satisfactory.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="469">Curiosity just leading into more curiosity...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="470">So, is that where you're feeling all of &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; yearning?</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="471">I did not expect to feel so... interested...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="472">Seems you are worthy of taking down...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="517">Whatever designer crafted you seems to have intended you for breeding...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="518">A penis that size is quite perverse, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="519">It would be my preference to work with something that can really make a splash...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="520">No wonder you were willing to play. You wanted to show off your toy...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="481">You're equipped with the right stuff...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="482">But does he have the strength and stamina to match...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="483">You... might be more than worthy...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="484">It might be difficult, but that could make it all the more pleasurable...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_1">Hm. I am still not even sure this one is human.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-mocking.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_1">The big ones are always dumb. That's just too bad for you, sponge-head.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_1">Nfufu. You backed yourself into a corner. What a moron...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1">I suspect you have another trick up your sleeve... or lack thereof.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-defiant.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_1">Your antics have grown tiresome. You'd better not be wearing more underwear this time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-defiant.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_1">That is enough. Put an end to this farce!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Jura_s0_1">Hm. Certainly never heard anything about sending humans out into space. Doesn't seem safe for them, especially so many.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-playful.png" marker="Nephenee_s1_1">Oh! The behelmed human takes another turn! Nfufu...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Nephenee_s2_1">How is it that you fight, ~nephenee~? I know you're rather limited in your options, but I am curious...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Nephenee_s3_1">You must have some occupation outside of being a soldier, ~nephenee~. Well?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Nephenee_s4_1">I like the funny way you talk, ~nephenee~. Say something else funny.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Nephenee_s5_1">Are you really not going to take your helmet off? Ever?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Nephenee_s6_1">So what's it gonna be, ~nephenee~? Helmet or debase yourself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Nephenee_s0_1">I'm not used to seeing humans in battle gear...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Meia_s0_1">You seem to be dressed for a fight. Quite unusual, for a human.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Roll_s0_1">... And what exactly do we have here?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="15">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, well, well! Look who came shuffling back!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="AquaKH_s0_1">
                    <text>... Remind me again what it is you're named. I want to say it starts with a "Q?" ... Quanda.</text>
                    <operations>
                        <nickname character="aqua_kh" op="=" name="Quanda" weight="0" />
                    </operations>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="AquaKS_s0_1">It is your turn. Do something amusing, human. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="AquaGrunt_s0_1">
                    <text>What was your name again, human? Grunt? What sort of thing do you do, Grunt?</text>
                    <operations>
                        <nickname character="magma_grunt" op="=" name="Grunt" weight="0" />
                    </operations>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="aoi_asahina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Aoi_s0_1">Okay, let's have it then, human. What is it that you do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="magma_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="MagmaGrunt_s0_1">
                    <text>You. Magnus or whatever. What's your story? You strike me as woefully unremarkable.</text>
                    <operations>
                        <nickname character="magma_grunt" op="=" name="Magnus" weight="0" />
                    </operations>
                </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="0" saidMarker="leviathan_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Nephenee_s0_2">No, the humans don't. Most of them just run away and hide. All the fighting is done by reploids.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="1" saidMarker="leviathan_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Nephenee_s1_2">But you are human, aren't you? I've never heard of a... "beorc."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="2" saidMarker="leviathan_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Nephenee_s2_2">Really? Nfufu. The blue armor. The lance. You almost seem like a primitive version of me! Tell me, are you a strong swimmer too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="3" saidMarker="leviathan_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Nephenee_s3_2">Farming? You mean raising animals and plants for food? &lt;i&gt;That's&lt;/i&gt; what you do?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="4" saidMarker="leviathan_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Nephenee_s4_2">Oh? Embarrassing? Even more embarrassing than having to show us your naked body?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="5" saidMarker="leviathan_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Nephenee_s5_2">You &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt;? If you &lt;i&gt;need to&lt;/i&gt;? So in your hierarchy of embarrassment, someone seeing the top of your head ranks nearly the same as being seen masturbating?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="6" saidMarker="leviathan_resp6_1" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png" marker="Nephenee_s6_2">Oh--- &lt;i&gt;come on&lt;/i&gt;! You can't be serious! Take the damn helmet off already!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="1">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;Kyah!&lt;/i&gt; What in the world?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="2">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Now spare us your sentimentality and get on with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="3">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Great. Now what is he up to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png">... You couldn't possibly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ghh! Eww! Wh-what in the---</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good. If you didn't put him on ice, I was going to do it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="13">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png">... Huh, there she goes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="16">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">You're being overly weird about this, human. It is making it difficult to enjoy your humiliation...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="19">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformation" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Grrrrreat... now what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Cat_transformation" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Now what is one up to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Just when it looked like you were ready to give up...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu. Will it be enough to save you?</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Oh. I was hoping you had forgotten about ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Hmm, what a convenient little excuse not to give up here and now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What's this ? A fail-safe?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Interesting that your last bastion doesn't hide all that much.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Did you forget you had ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ or something?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Struggling to maintain your crumbling foothold?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="7" saidMarker="leviathan_resp6_2" />
                <condition count="2" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Nephenee_s6_3x">W-wait a second... if I had let you keep your helmet &lt;i&gt;I would have won!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="1" saidMarker="leviathan_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Nephenee_s0_3">I had already figured there are no reploids where you're from. If there were, there wouldn't be any need for you to fight at all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="2" saidMarker="leviathan_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Nephenee_s1_3">
                    <text>The only person I'm implying isn't human is me... but very well. If it means that much to you, I will refrain from calling you that. I will just call you by your name... Nepty?</text>
                    <operations>
                        <nickname character="nephenee" op="=" name="Nepty" weight="0" />
                    </operations>
                </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="3" saidMarker="leviathan_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Nephenee_s2_3">Let's not get bogged down in the semantics. Prehistoric, antiquated, outmoded, obsolete, ancient, prototypical, barbaric. Take your pick, ~nephenee~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="4" saidMarker="leviathan_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png" marker="Nephenee_s3_3">Ugh. That sounds like it would involve a lot of dirt. Hot dry dirt...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="5" saidMarker="leviathan_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-cross.png" marker="Nephenee_s4_3">Oh, of course. With breasts like that, who would have anything but unmitigated praise?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="6" saidMarker="leviathan_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Nephenee_s5_3">Well, at least you have a full head of hair down there to show us...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nephenee" stage="7" saidMarker="leviathan_resp6_2" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png" marker="Nephenee_s6_3">There we go. Now I can savor all the delicious embarrassment spread across your pretty little face. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="24">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="4" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Despite all appearances, it seems you really &lt;i&gt;aren't&lt;/i&gt; human. Hm... well, you're human enough, probably.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="30">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Gguh... as if it weren't clear enough you weren't human...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Okay. There's a lot about what just happened that I need explained...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">At least you were a bit amusing before you failed horribly. I anticipate your humiliation will be even more amusing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="9">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">There's something wrong with this guy! C-can a human become maverick?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">That's not funny!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-cross.png">I guess something even dumber than before is more or less the logical progression of things...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Huh. Maybe that's where all your brain power went.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="14">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">And this is her stand-in? Curious thing, but not nearly as enticing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="17">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So that's it? Well, boy or girl matters very little to me. You're still a cute little thing! Nfufu!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-envious.png">Oh... you're a man? Ugh, and for a moment I thought were were both...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="21">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformed" />
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">H-h-huh? Wh-what? She made her--- now hers are--- that's &lt;i&gt;cheating!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="22">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu. A fairly underwhelming transformation, but you are cuter like this. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4" id="23">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformed" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'll never understand the human preoccupation with fat...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">You're already so exposed! You really should just give it up!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm not going to complain. Watching you struggle is half the fun!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">Defeating you will be all the more satisfying if I truly take everything from you!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How thrilling it is to have you so exposed and still so desperate to win. Nfufu! You're fun! I like you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I had just begun to think of ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ as part of your body.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">They always struggle the hardest right at the end...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Don't tell me you got cold feet after flaunting your body like that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And here I thought you were committed to being a pervert.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="649">Well, now it's official. You suck!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="650">Of course you couldn't keep it together in the end. No big surprise!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="651">Well, that was fun, but I do believe you now owe us a whole load more of fun.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="652">I'm convinced you wanted to lose. A pervert like you has probably been dying to touch yourself since before we started.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="665">I knew you were bound to screw up eventually. And you did! Multiple times!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="666">I expected more from you. Oh, wait, no I didn't! Nfufu!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="667">Blame bad luck as much as you want. It all boils down to you just not being better than me!</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="668">You had a few good rounds and you got cocky. Let this be a lesson in humility and in my superiority!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="673">Nfufu. Had to be someone, didn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="674">What's the matter? Got horny and lost your edge?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="675">Almost as satisfying as defeating you myself.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Think of this as your last chance to prove yourself. I'll be watching, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, I'm not immune from distraction myself. Maybe if you put on a good show, you'll end up seeing a bit more from me...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I suppose you could still prove yourself competent at &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; activities.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu. Despite everything, I do hope you have a good time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="704">Well... consider yourself lucky to receive the same punishment as me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="705">Still, you managed to outlast me. That is impressive...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="706">At least you can finally give into those urges my beauty has inspired in you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="679">I won't hear any complaints. You got in over your head on your own accord. Now let's watch you swim...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="681">Now, don't be sour. You really should try and enjoy this...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="682">If I were you, I'd be beside myself with joy right now. You get to pleasure yourself while in the very presence of my beauty.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="680">I hope you last longer at this than you did with the game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Hmm... your pathetic face does make me want to tease you...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu. You look so aroused it must be uncomfortable. Maybe you should beg for release...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why be gentle with yourself? I certainly would not be...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ah... the shape. Just right for pushing inside and spreading apart...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Hmm... ~target~... if I focus just so... I can feel it too...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Are you trying to forget I'm watching, ~target~? If anything, that should turn you on more...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I bet yours is warm to the touch...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Would you pursue your partner's pleasure as diligently as you do your own?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Mmm... I do keep wondering... if ~target~'s would be a good fit...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Hnn... to feel ~target~ twitching... as I tighten around him...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">To have a such a thing inside me... being pleased by me...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Don't stop... ~target~. Not until I've... nngh...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Haah... to give pleasure to another... to have their satisfaction... hinge on you... hnnn...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Nnngh... just look at my pussy. It's made itself ready for someone... someone like ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Imagining these things... pales in comparison to seeing them. ~Target~'s gotten me so wet...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">This is not intended... just for my pleasure, ~target~. It is for pleasing someone like you too...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I'm sure having my beauty right before you is an excellent boon, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nfufu. What a pathetic face you're making. Does it feel good?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">No stopping until you're all the way done!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Don't stop, ~target~. It's bad enough you lost. Don't reveal you've got no stamina either.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Look at me if you want. It's only natural that my design would spark desire in you.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Not running out of steam yet, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Losers ought to put in a bit more effort for the winners...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Show us how far your lust will reach, ~target~! Get even more in touch with your baser instincts!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="716">This... is quite the new sensation...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="717">Nfufu. I feel peculiarly warm after that...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="718">Now there's a look that could melt ice...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="719">Hmm... I think I really am quite impressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Mnn... hnn? E-everything was white... f-for a moment...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ggghhn... my body... felt... hhhah...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">T-to have that inside me when that happens... I'd be... a m-mess...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nfufu. Look at her! She's had a plan ready to go for when she loses! Well, let's see what it is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="649">Just like I thought. In the end, no match for me.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="650">You can't have expected to win against me. Losing must have been your goal this whole time.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="651">Looks like you're about to be retired. Unfortunately, you don't get to just bow out.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="652">A superior reploid can't be beat. Not even at something like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="673">I didn't expect a cute girl like you was going to get away so easy.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="674">Nfufu. You should see the look on your face.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="675">Not so high-and-mighty now, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="665">You came far only to fail so hard. Pretty much what I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="666">You had more fight in you than I thought, but not that much more!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="667">I would never underestimate another woman. Case in point, I was right about being able to defeat you.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="668">You tried, you really did. That just makes it all the more pathetic that you lost.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, this is quite inventive. I'd never say no to a little moisture myself, but I'll give you your privacy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Now, let's see how a woman like you handles herself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Try not to shrink under my watchful eye. Or do. You're cute when you're embarrassed.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Nfufu. This may not work out so well for me. I'm liable to let myself get distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I do suppose the game is over for you now. No reason you can't begin to relax and do it as you please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="704">Hmm, lucky for me. My imagination is a bit lacking.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="705">This should make my admiration of you... much more exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="706">Hopefully I haven't left you high and dry so far...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="679">Feel free to appreciate my beauty as you tend to yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="681">Try not and view it as a punishment. It should feel good...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="682">I know looking at me has probably filled you with all sorts of interesting feelings, so now is the perfect time to work them out.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="680">You shouldn't have any problem getting started, seeing you're already showing signs of arousal...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You were already so aroused. No point in denying it. I'm not immune to these things myself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Will you be satisfied with just this?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmm... she makes the whole business of losing look good...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">She looks like she's enjoying herself. I'd certainly enjoy her too...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">That's the look of pleasure, isn't it? Your body feels good, doesn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nfufu. If I don't look away from ~target~, I'm bound to wind up just like her...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Hoo... she's even more beautiful like this...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Is this embarrassing for you, ~target~? Would it be better if someone else tended to you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Hmm... a warm touch... like ~target~'s...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">I keep seeing ~target~'s face of pleasure and... I...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Looking at ~target~ it's like I can feel her pleasure coursing through me...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">It's so much better... together...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Oh... the things I would have her... haah... do to me...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Hnnph... ~target.toStutter(1)~...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu... how do you feel, ~target~? If it's anything like I do... hnn...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I'm just feeling so... and ~target~ is... I d-didn't...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">If you want to gaze upon me for inspiration, then you won't hear me complain!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">She really ought to indulge herself even more. What good is it to let this opportunity slip by?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nfufu! You really should see the faces you're making!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Don't stop until your legs shake so much you can't stand!</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">This opportunity may never come back around. Make the most of it.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Looks like you're handling your defeat pretty well...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, ~target~, all your effort does make me feel like a winner.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu! Just look at ~target~. Practically begging for a mate...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="25">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Cat_End" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nfufu! So good you lost your concentration, it seems! How very scandalous...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Chubby_End" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Huh... and they shrunk right back. Still sort of big though...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="27">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" sayingMarker="Chubby_End" />
                <state img="#-envious.png">Hmph. If they got both ways, why stop while they're still so big?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="716">Feeling... jealous all of a sudden...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="717">When the moment came... you looked so sexy...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="718">I wasn't even sure I could get shivers...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="719">Nfufu... I'm very, &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; pleased with how you turned out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Am I... capable of something that s-sublime...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">S-something... just from that...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">W-what's this... &lt;i&gt;warmth&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="825">Just like I thought. In the end, no match for me.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="826">You can't have expected to win against me. Losing must have been your goal this whole time.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="827">Looks like you're about to be retired. Unfortunately, you don't get to just bow out.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="828">A superior reploid can't be beat. Not even at something like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="837">You came far only to fail so hard. Pretty much what I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="838">You had more fight in you than I thought, but not that much more!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="839">I would never underestimate another woman. Case in point, I was right about being able to defeat you.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="840">You tried, you really did. That just makes it all the more pathetic that you lost.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="856">I didn't expect a cute girl like you was going to get away so easy.</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png" oneShotId="857">Nfufu. You should see the look on your face.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="858">Not so high-and-mighty now, are you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="919">Feel free to appreciate my beauty as you tend to yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="920">Try not and view it as a punishment. It should feel good...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="921">I know looking at me has probably filled you with all sorts of interesting feelings, so now is the perfect time to work them out.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="922">You shouldn't have any problem getting started, seeing you're already showing signs of arousal...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Now, let's see how a woman like you handles herself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Try not to shrink under my watchful eye. Or do. You're cute when you're embarrassed.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Nfufu. This may not work out so well for me. I'm liable to let myself get distracted...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I do suppose the game is over for you now. No reason you can't begin to relax and do it as you please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="931">Hmm, lucky for me. My imagination is a bit lacking.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="932">This should make my admiration of you... much more exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png" oneShotId="933">Hopefully I haven't left you high and dry so far...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">I'm sure having my beauty right before you is an excellent boon, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nfufu. What a pathetic face you're making. Does it feel good?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">No stopping until you're all the way done!</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Don't stop, ~target~. It's bad enough you lost. Don't reveal you've got no stamina either.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Look at me if you want. It's only natural that my design would spark desire in you.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Not running out of steam yet, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Losers ought to put in a bit more effort for the winners...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Show us how far your lust will reach, ~target~! Get even more in touch with your baser instincts!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6 8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Hmm... your pathetic face does make me want to tease you...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Nfufu. You look so aroused it must be uncomfortable. Maybe you should beg for release...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why be gentle with yourself? I certainly would not be...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ah... the shape. Just right for pushing inside and spreading apart...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Hmm... ~target~... if I focus just so... I can feel it too...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Are you trying to forget I'm watching, ~target~? If anything, that should turn you on more...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">I bet yours is warm to the touch...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Would you pursue your partner's pleasure as diligently as you do your own?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Mmm... I do keep wondering... if ~target~'s would be a good fit...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Hnn... to feel ~target~ twitching... as I tighten around her...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">To have a such a thing inside me... being pleased by me...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Don't stop... ~target~. Not until I've... nngh...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Haah... to give pleasure to another... to have their satisfaction... hinge on you... hnnn...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Nnngh... just look at my pussy. It's made itself ready for someone... someone like ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Imagining these things... pales in comparison to seeing them. ~Target~'s gotten me so wet...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">This is not intended... just for my pleasure, ~target~. It is for pleasing someone like you too...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="947">This... is quite the new sensation...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="948">Nfufu. I feel peculiarly warm after that...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png" oneShotId="949">Now there's a look that could melt ice...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png" oneShotId="950">Hmm... I think I really am quite impressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Mnn... hnn? E-everything was white... f-for a moment...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">Ggghhn... my body... felt... hhhah...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">T-to have that inside me when that happens... I'd be... a m-mess...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Th-there's no way! Me?! Defeated?! By you? Rrrgh! How did this happen?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">H-how frustrating! For me to lose! It's unbelievable! How could it be?</state>
                <state img="#-frustrated.png">Y-you all are so... so frustrating! How could it be that I'm the one who ended up defeated like this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="nephenee" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Nephenee_s6_3x" />
                <state img="#-displeased.png" marker="Nephenee_Finalx">&lt;i&gt;Of course&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Somehow... I've been defeated. Maybe I just got careless...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">So frustrating... but a loss is a loss. No matter how unbelievable it is.</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Even after I tried... hmph! This is all so frustrating. This shouldn't have been so hard...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="opp" character="nephenee" saidMarker="Leviathan_Finalx" />
                <state img="#-lost.png">Nfufu. I guess I'll have to pay extra special attention to myself as punishment...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-lost.png">Nfufu. At least it's not a total loss. Now I can finally take care of something that's been bothering me...</state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">... But I don't really feel like complaining all that much. There's only one thing I do feel like doing now...</state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">Fine. If I have to be a loser, then I should dedicate myself to doing the best job I can.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Hoo... there it is. I can feel it... spreading through my whole body...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Haah... this whole thing is... so silly...</state>
                <state img="#-defiant.png">Nnnff... I need to hurry... to the good part...</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">Hhaah... haaah! J-just a slight t-touch is enou--- haaah, haaanh!</state>
                <state img="#-envious.png">I-It's fine... but it's... better underwater...</state>
                <state img="#-flirting.png">Nnn... it's so good...  can't... c-can't...</state>
                <state img="#-horny.png">F-feeling so tense... taut with p-pleasure...</state>
                <state img="#-mocking.png">This is the best someone unworthy can hope for...</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Too bad I... I only have my hand to work with...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">F-feels so strange... b-but so good...</state>
                <state img="#-ready.png">Nfufu. Don't get any funny ideas. I don't do that sort of thing on dry land...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">So much... so much... but I need more...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Enjoying the view, pervs? Take it all in. This might be your only chance.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I should take care of myself m-more often...</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Tch... ooh... it's hard not to go overboard... so I'll j-just go overboard...</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">Hmm... the feeling is a lot different from being underwater...</state>
                <state img="#-yawn.png">&lt;i&gt;Kyaah!&lt;/i&gt; Haah... th-that may have been... too much...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Ghaa... aaah... c-cumming... cumming!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Nfufu... nhaa... I'm just about...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Grrgh... c-can't keep... c-can't...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">More... before I... h-haah...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">It's going... to be a big one...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">N-n-no! T-too much! Ghhaa... haah!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-climax.png">Ky-&lt;i&gt;aaaaaaahn!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">... H-huh? Oh... j-just... give me a second...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">S-sinking... I'm on solid ground... and I'm sinking...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">... M-mission... complete...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-yawn.png">Haa... tiring work, masturbation.</state>
                <state img="#-wondering.png">It's too bad not each one of you can pay for humiliating me.</state>
                <state img="#-uppity.png">Well, maybe I would go through all this again. With all of you. In order to correctly humiliate you.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is taking longer than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm not leaving until I witness everything there is to see!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I did have fun... even if losing is that frustrated.</state>
                <state img="#-playful.png">Nfufu. It felt good to get up to some mischief.</state>
                <state img="#-displeased.png">It's so dusty up here. When can I get back in the water?</state>
                <state img="#-cross.png">I'm not here for moral support. I'm here for... whatever the opposite of moral support is. Vicious mockery? That sounds right.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">This is... not a normal human social activity, right? This is special and strange, right?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This is fun and all, but I'd really rather do the whole thing underwater!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm surprised humans would play a game that takes so long. You do only have so long to live, after all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition filterOut="robot" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, I guess I couldn't expect humans like you to be a challenge for me. At least it was fun humiliating you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Not lucky enough. Try again sometime.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-playful.png">Okay, clothes back on and lets go again! Don't tell me you're too tired to keep playing!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Even among reploids, I am superior. Winning was just an inevitability. At least it was fun.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Alright, game's over. No more free peeks.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Nfufu. I'll get you next time, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="custom:phase_strip">Well played. I'll be seeing you again, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
